[{"topicId":"20","id":"20000","langCode":"vi","question":"rdCDUtpV0w5KErnkBotRwa1OkUdVgKT/NW5uSIMCnTFNoe5t2wi8uSoBWg+hRzmgGpzIj2PnKpseXNowtA6xYg\u003d\u003d","answers":["as colorful","colorfuler","colorful","more colorful"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE76VDA22tfq6n0K8dDGbsuxXVoLfUUJSyHm0QspCVIp+DTMubdGggXIa1trOOR2TIcp/LPqaA0AvFHE7UPYOKAzffDyryRyW39mGfv2yFgENDvR4CShkrp9F6XWxJjjRYfUPFYsUKwRMoknTb/JZeXMNqWYtuEs7cUb7T7/FCQtRg4MMUoBlyBpa3cxbH7skviGVjXh19YWGglDm6yvPg2JMDUiQNHXDZSE18/XgWdH9nPsrHrJ5mauvEQmqQ8IedarBZsCCS8z51vaIPCEQwh5omfPHyYfi/q43XjWTIwwJmDK0unQkpG42XOK0WL81pFhxOuIuDZ+qScvksvBnKb+BuUHI2bjRoVH80Dfz4Q/mTbInvWzQsIZrPPtbYdquUTGYl0xDHJyTtBdK4802PYA02GXgiFDXstly8Ltiu8+wrn+qDkdZ8OzKGVEk6n2C9ppsg4k/Ss+VuIpujoHQs4K9hSAAWxb+5wKWPFgLIorryUZsezPz9qsBh6vBalL/XnB8xac44f3LANp55pTArFACAny7RgeNGyhjXWVw37bwEUCYiUgDw724ltwEuyacCjtE5xJoAJ5hFQP1NpKK8H/5gElgcAQrtM1RDzbQ/AfCH2PCgJ1Mv5WYtgZT9WH3IA+hHrFQuM+Fp2Z1UQZSUSM\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20001","langCode":"vi","question":"UCwZtIo/5sZ+c12B1xFYiPrliE6fx8Nt1ViZ8WatKSN7vbTaMBXg+Qy6B1vq1sCrXcR/xZauE7qVPe0Ab++whsfd4zFtzi+kdPrnCm3C4ik\u003d","answers":["dry than","dry","dry as","drier"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5X9FUamnuMLT0PxW8VbFXJN8pEzIbFCRINhf2mRvbYk7uT6p6+ndYChge5TiX8fzZdDJKugr2rIqs0ExpQxoplh0REixH7aK/qLuEBuQq/udP9j3xNNxeqlHBEimJ2HLvqkMNoGbIkq5/x3Zd6eu9nde3ETHJmtqxfs1mNs63X/pdZKKETtZYTsI21tMaeYoTd8TyKeGfzg6zRkmQ83Gee4YZB5Oy63tpGsyKoLlLB1p2lvbKe9HuBX6VGyxqW/VvqJiClbDVf3Ftc57AgeyPSsOE5x0STqWrvML5zNzMYcOP/tDnqcGKhk5GX5XTZIeHbSALljTqmMSpPEPVG6DbGaxeGNKLJnEi128q6uWqFjgGymRm+54tcDvctsrWKB+HflEaY4KQ1ZUU2FY8QkCMuj3j+bePF33M+bdZ6couqTbG6MWXsI5al/0Uk8C1bM9dg2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF29htPysOd+whUrgrCYSqW5sEANjO1PtUzhHEIJyIv4oiSTtaXFs01PErgmcMG+wq/FskEaiXI0hwXJDgZ/b/YhnWJZ22NnDxBSyTUfzZp4RWMoKWJXEt9jLRmdY6Zr3sGgBlQWUcdLHznJaBbEYJgOyo55GMi6PTN7QPiVloD6V+w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20002","langCode":"vi","question":"+uy1cCcrPf/GnHzrJrIdmEJa/qWwwv5DgPHxd0AzL4pRjbYsBf/RBxkB86hLdDD800yDwc3IQclyzx1rGP94Og\u003d\u003d","answers":["more good","as good","well","good"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwzbrHEwLWKXGo2lS9aR8LK/y9XEZ24vn7wSkmnQBUE9iBpL+D+j/BNTx7VwGKlPzwHs7RCLBOTK/VUZbauuleGe26KPehHM4ejirUBBfSmTr/F42MUWGeG7tRFCTMFpl3D1xWsDNJG0Ro4SXH6E9nY12zJobyLbg/0wN3wQJ7IK9HoGMdJfdTcCvo9gHdfeaP9Gsy3xsHFmghZW9hwW+iWIYMkuKig3ohYYeidDRqJw3mD3qb42aTGnMiy9PkXM/4oT642LxoUxLAfbvtAxp26BxXY6ukiFT/JdyEJx3Tu1rGAiS/Gbk79nOVZCVaCfJT0B5HMS8cyHA99W/p7xYXPnT6MRZJCQgjHVsJsPqymBTOMwtUF5Lipm/kAAGGPtU1ldYLOO7dEHsEomEngUKVW65qNh7LJcfc8FTk/HzAyEDi2sgfzZFnbMQKmhNY3PFhDpiBDDOhYFXelHN1oZw7IJHq5ukZupy78F8Gw8iMTNUOQUf8r7OUlewfxrN2jOrceck84pN7OED5FVlqxAEmppK7ITrunHR3kDxH7zcwEZcHcNpa0tBzoRyUhz2Vo7dfEqmpwru0ZmhoFxy1vOkkjhNb9RBUhDKuF14NxwmjNYRUA6mWlE2dw8BeCA2EG00w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20003","langCode":"vi","question":"DGhTdxhKDggch+5HYtM7SpekvniNyfDU4bImGNXXXhi0YiB2mLaVDNkmCPl9Lr/E/5liG818SLATGrybaN5T/EqnmPWJiMMG+Wa9iWEabSugwXdibYGlgr5gGNfq5TGS","answers":["worse","bad than","bad","bad as"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+F7MdE5+1+aF2n+t7VQIDhN8pEzIbFCRINhf2mRvbYk5iPlaXTdL2zqzvtBGiW+dz+EGX1kCLkTYYhh2mATFwROIHJwgx4DAohQING6EC5PTvi+q8R2MpmaCIVcNSxZn6TisA7+eiJGf1Gf/NlDCh2g+CDtcMT+1KPz40HtvLYF2oPc9vhyqmXYXs0KjK0GDRer0x1M5VhfiZrSmf5EcGifizfzjCm7Vu9uruYDH2Nnd84BoqxOUZgwoDfb5JOI8l8OPMCUVupUZV6IpAP/Nikn89MqhE9bJFo+6xoYTu0I9oXg4jW8xUnnxa0sI81PRB/txaKhkb7zdI9y9iT2GNkwfU/veUaNbpxx0HJWRsneGJpPH0trtSHuV3pf4i42fxbk9C9S/6yXVRuPjThNy+lxxWJbrPPqjknkuFH2tBGfKtl6qfDDGqmFJb4ZgwYAtPgL+d6U4lvEtwzQUtPPRf+4InaziAXbwiC047zuw1XVZwy+C9/jcLrCMX49Na3O4s23/mf0HlaWd7xsqfrvsvVzcp9+HlBE5Uy0NlBZKdedEqdpYrSAWCmU4z2d+njLbBwDrpr75Loru8ZHZbs2wVPGG0JOXsGGHtXDqWb1IkB1aQ+8i0cPA1Rg0qm3fRjHvOMBKUMkHbBYRdM8qIiThrGYiqwIjFS8aaopZVSpVTBN"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20004","langCode":"vi","question":"qJna5UkMjpHRiKVi25wgjP+vngdViCSNRTN3JlsbPLOEDaOYgHeK+ZuHLgmTbyvhFycFbhGSjadZGPgr5zpoCA\u003d\u003d","answers":["more carefully","carefully","as carefully","less carefully"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7SsMaO3IovKHq+/j8CqPPMn2QMGlrrwKoO5wwJD7Pjo5yPN2UZrG0KJppsJKqNDX2dK6AAbVC5z9xeSMEVb7w8P3+Hn/7u2uPy5TN8M0L/GxPgPjwPvFwdayO4yHozlVk74vqvEdjKZmgiFXDUsWZ+k4rAO/noiRn9Rn/zZQwodoPgg7XDE/tSj8+NB7by2BdqD3Pb4cqpl2F7NCoytBg0Xq9MdTOVYX4ma0pn+RHBon4s384wpu1bvbq7mAx9jZ3fOAaKsTlGYMKA32+STiPJfDjzAlFbqVGVeiKQD/zYpJ/PTKoRPWyRaPusaGE7tCPaF4OI1vMVJ58WtLCPNT0Qf7cWioZG+83SPcvYk9hjZMH1P73lGjW6ccdByVkbJ3tNi1jCjkNc7TqEvwjDcpgqHS88Vh4Q1TtYGkyZicDeWrEo10eppmk55/C26iLwkqCEU903RhC43fxsNPMFrWQf8VsfptPxRQFqm9UA5Sr5E6p/9c1kt65gEMhfb6yrWnNg2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF28HC8KbGUypAl+QLpNSixlh9Ob94QjGcnL4jkrNXEZa8N8bW4OxtVtMhLnBzhS71HYBCQOxN84cNDe1Oow7nMsZUEQaVWHeQ+jwcDmNP+IYsIq0nXUVZG4J32V1HIY0MzVqwrFlaQ16K3FRH5uMAzr0IPATbQFxCRlmgxaqsEfZ/7BLMCPv9DuIncHCdP9Qdqwpt0uEY5HpYGHrExZ//5D0"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20005","langCode":"vi","question":"lBKWFaN5eGL9169063l0GUaX1N2k3bnqpoehTsX5onyhOv0c9ne5U7B1AZaTMLxWXlL4OHevEUjSMaHr7D4pHw\u003d\u003d","answers":["as much money than","much money as","more much money as","as much money as"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/v/w4iy2mRJWGvrigCC2DmULRzi3nHeuncS8q7+hT5Fwdz9x06nigKr+DSStizc3SEuRvQOszzHIekPIiqQcd7lJp45b04ndeK3WTwdO0yGfi26yUB0QHIw71j1C8jOTjzb8/zbd3zua1Ts/XO0YKEJ1v0jc+FEuCV7DhFpNM6xWWaNK65lq6Isii77gJNzOQk+XBpeqeP0UWH2Pcu0XdoFXi49NoyKKx/KRIWCuLFmaaNSk1VtPIyj06XEzB789Yb1BYLoh8VRD/RjyjzV/xjf9cvaLlcLe2nt0I9hKDSEIVSDo/TVtVorbUTj6kxMhYY2g5y4OOrQVStvNVZd6+Nf7wIsAG92vFtyGq20W7ZtiGFFmse0ac9kmWjxFssHcefzV230p+HxQzMZC2zUK4fSBFJpF5iVJL5aLxY/SkZtgQ1uaVJZkku19ti+UtKCarG4AJUz+TUwZiL9BS9qy51DqJ+Yp/hHs803Q3ly3yT5pOKwDv56IkZ/UZ/82UMKHaD4IO1wxP7Uo/PjQe28tgXag9z2+HKqZdhezQqMrQYNF6vTHUzlWF+JmtKZ/kRwaJ+LN/OMKbtW726u5gMfY2d3zgGirE5RmDCgN9vkk4jylTcDElS5U6BDc+ch5Sb0fhylyhpn0uVBvcpKzNTzkO7MPNN0FEb3gjUQWfvWh6V59d545aQRlw96UGTzIqRHv2p9grf3SsIFjkCJKwPECk7tpDT+B8LVRclXY8I2kkwPYQ4+dEs8xUo8sNJwDrdRLqrWCPP4NOW9E4ikDjJe0svy15UqgQyTO83XzfD7kXhKCOdnkkbNN7V9Y+2k2w0+GbMJyD2B7SnBQLd9I7LR57LJRmx7M/P2qwGHq8FqUv9ecHzFpzjh/csA2nnmlMCsUNwfbYF2YBp2Qba+sepEZmiDhrL38jv6M4VfAo1wTG5kr2+s5Nmksm75eOVFdE/h0Ofk2v2gr/KvtuKmLhc//9gYvE3PTwWmGgexYbPQFek++Vn0X0972iaelQmJtwvCaO0NZSe8EsAeJOHr/rJD/XSd9WJErqWRBMHP8RxKygN5/JagQUtiZnGEQXiJnyb/+4Slo3e0+QoZrg3SbJBWDkA\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20006","langCode":"vi","question":"EsYklG2MY3UMpRtMJr76lmlkP+TUBYpj7hPzWJP0E4IsC0MctNcdtq8GEH8Q/Kf78oIDPwoCktJlgucd+kuzFQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["many people","more many people","as many people","as much people"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8pw6mwZugcrgf9S1qSYdx470tme364kh1VEy/thgHrNC9ITYAPxbJf4OsfaBf4jtAHK+4u1WUaqkwXFKiGUWFAKbfL4b9935bW7qtfSbXKIH5gefCQap7DvkxPDmhu1nE74vqvEdjKZmgiFXDUsWZ+k4rAO/noiRn9Rn/zZQwodoPgg7XDE/tSj8+NB7by2BdqD3Pb4cqpl2F7NCoytBg0Xq9MdTOVYX4ma0pn+RHBon4s384wpu1bvbq7mAx9jZ3fOAaKsTlGYMKA32+STiPI83Ve/QAmaImUk+HAtPnlQdsSfwlzAEhsFuzNpgJSjv/L32+7zs5rkkroN0WH7gMBhQYavP0kedaojS9OCqwG6u3CVuVjBvxI7uqusfgSC1gCrAauyFOQN6WE+WP73PGlH7ASaToewzsjKG0h6wVqlIoMQAE4PJQjFwVusy/Lp+5genAEbFXJMkr1JUzeLmlEsDppHxkxs/Hl8BQU8p+mtDY7VbPiI/eyb0MnLXPhEvPwfg4aTvZElMAoPbWim9cBf9iZOMq4zWKag7kT5qJGB1tLUnJxCUIUhYhRyHhEyQfy2Vg4NY9JIf5B1ds/wLusD/cVD7CRHgtCBFN05opzbCK3uvcVO9a0Napantk0sdKBuD8O0jthGC7uEILgMtV3ZGf7/1itoDctFaL3AwMSgV3VHlT1jTc/eayWDRvtsB1kWfr9Z1ztvh3aIdQwskmxAhpc6+QqFG4+pPieayL+vXDUKJz1OZS/9PhZW8BZAj0fsBJpOh7DOyMobSHrBWqUigxAATg8lCMXBW6zL8un78ds+NhhsJVXxrwPkwZbOcNg2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF29j/MOi+HOpvyIZJMMz5YETyv25+FmSmkvEt6NmvcfIb0PL8V2f++dTiIMQcNclKBzyGB2ixcG1m30mKfTFBYN7pkEZfg92nHZl46fjDIHD3CKkrUA9kS6mZB4fOwol4oKk31hcsPv4ULneOoJDKb39neYZEX3LNa24YqqKyc/OWLptooZ1JQbEqL2bdWGK5Wg\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20007","langCode":"vi","question":"oLcqHtT/jf4cl3MwWoH97Xhj+H6a5z9KMzsRzjakh3QStfDhsbDw+oEpC/kX0nEpnsyQ0sO3lgTmemCWRmCsqXpspiPnjg2JunVo40NgfDOEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh","answers":["3,000 times","as much as 3,000 times","as much than 3,000 times","more much as 3,000 times"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/v/w4iy2mRJWGvrigCC2DnEATU4ovwCA1E4na8QL69/71I6pR8QgrH4wtKf/8Cog6nRrUQwanEym3C/yQQ9fHhCNM0WBI5UOPAvBCOVMTDev4CakHEbDZLKrAKURyIIGRbWCtsm7Ye1Gjqqt90vSukt9k3QD42WJ/zipGQkC/CPz9WxzL2A/W0G62gi4EVeDACgzErswknvJeepMXwkBKcfihJKlfYhjFh0a02lg+HZKX4xMIOyQM+QNOT6yWVcId+VwMXtmRSvNm4Pomhzenlqb3M1QN8ThgJxBlosiPzApXvh0T5tXfOylsVBv8sWVPM051OqXclT5pbdHlebGxQcB67sfDPHuFoH8k2sLBpjC9WYFREaUBoBTYs3V2UGrFao/JNjp8FC7fs6isJ2mWa4DVxjn+imEB/o6QuIHjitCKtXS0JEhgqmKB6Kg18Cc9VsQZmcybkYm05iev4vHuVNsie9bNCwhms8+1th2q5RPFiFD96xaqhUZMFw2WcVXRucMuc5JWr11ZwLOtaGpUtxxWJbrPPqjknkuFH2tBGfcxa3ew3oZgaQTiA3OFpbsZYbjtZSvnah+Rng8CbkCHKlV6QyeE129dfMjqu5JVsYT/QRcuhVXBEZzDdva/1uU9YhNMiTq6+KoxbOwKTxgZv9V7RnA6IbUr6I8CfjKt1H9NrhK1Mf7IPupnUIP63nV2yzZqWnYxoezvHtLb4HUovTZHm0APlt5Rb2OhSHWG7jwmW9azZe8sne6d7jJyeNLbxfwhA0GvrJcrFSqPPSySKhs2eN6yrM0mVd0gR9fxjR41Y1xeXZmAI+aIUM5KNY0jGV6g68ChYKocaAedQmm65hG/E0oJAny+F70Tjmmaab2fyxCxAs7dpVoS8TuVAV4yUvl48LL+eSexL1YVJZYneb7DgaDwpGN5vtru5V/gzYzXOR0vuHXbtfF2UOgMhMbvIMzcT6rbXX7/e7+CdEVO1zYpEImr/XZBu8phfhJSyjzIuwjWSACGZAzDb2HztoZ531N8GVvE0EcoNNQSCvnWS6lMo/mhZy7Gs3AC5H82KeFGHHKpjNt2hzM9xarq1aunkntPsU9mIXmabddJ4sFoxWz0l7JDhFJfQRmKBGwyJrcMxMzMi6LUQ9JAgjxDltOXjt9PBuVAX+EmmmPCyS4uzWNVq/yttpdO4pg8e1t5xU"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20008","langCode":"vi","question":"sFpVyp+cUq5ZSK37yzYOrSs629SaDDsPexCekTbrhMni57gFgHa3TgHx8rY8Lmhg","answers":["50 people","more many as 50 people","as many than 50 people","as many as 50 people"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8pw6mwZugcrgf9S1qSYdx56ekMlmjAqTi33uQlJVEuZLXKHXOEnFZz/65AyXIQQ66nf8xSdfsnfGFk668ihu0JV8mcV3FKkL7UVH/6fXxIqcdeSntXHnDFvXxAKiBZDjQyonaRk8qW2rALX01rx6iZspOwI21pddGIamK8WpvtuboqpUIdjWPIBoIM9WsceEXz2oafBPw7SznMlkZ0c8m7qRy1a1L1yayJqn0Hdd69mkIVUMu5Vr0HKgqNQSxLz+DL9rTUCuZuteGJb6lHCVwS9hAP0UmyMyle1bI4edloQUKgZ3PKbfyKmPVyr6n/ME4k7tDOi9LeuysiYbnk26fIpDHeYp9AbxcKSPDbGnNNW/+c9k3vKkIK6v5WYeJxz50iUoTrQB/YqWSbI3Hc1Ad+pC4l/aoI18XyOaWyLsbGgiTWr77GMZYK0jo+bR3rR6ZK+AW8ThlOXxxWyH9JY4t5JPXQvNfj+aTwPDCulW9UgU4AKPDVPvC6toXFzy3yzOG5zcvhu1ulwjhxYwwlSglehzxYo/6VTUSo2ntHkW3d+vRliTEEdQWWoL858TLecV97U3PWyi5pqnMw8Pc0uzo+tIoxDOIf03JZtuUTowhsL5jhCMzBYOJp2KL2Z/z7rPDLwMUm1jkMH1glcjCHDNvS68NiVTZY+zx5uS5nxSZOznIwDWUXrsqaspXj8toAMHqyz4Oq0Ev2/juOR8kCXGCN5ilQV5EZusxmT4LbTni+kbdsTCsI2m5IuiFaaX2Df7lUMOjX9cUPBs9AMfrXcgF0iz2ax+1gcHZlMWAJmFWiiubmJDpOrczh5/LvRwTzoBB/7003GfCVCMvT1ypBWXu14+2HO73UDiIQiFDXdRN4PId5t8Zaw+HdLAmatqytZyeIyDDSeyF2gj1CeHHrXhRqErtxBaOvJtSSiOS8A07aYyUZsezPz9qsBh6vBalL/XnB8xac44f3LANp55pTArFBl3kd8/UKFKuj8HJtQSlZuQEQN7R6K1op8F2mG5Dzjmtcq4sqfegWIxQYbSs0jSiz4mfBLYmIp6myUAqp7KwB7y7LJnH1qpTI5fXwKAosGpnPuiB8+uOrwI8j2a0EN9asg8BNtAXEJGWaDFqqwR9n/sEswI+/0O4idwcJ0/1B2rCm3S4RjkelgYesTFn//kPQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20009","langCode":"vi","question":"ZePJb/QgI1HSuyuNxPuRCFB7T/C90llYdEkdvH3AZprsMc0buVB4NBEMj+OFIjxJzVkQAobEHsCSiLZN0dFZf1/MvZSwQdLM0fAH8OQ+eK8\u003d","answers":["more heavy","not as heavy","as heavy","heavy"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/W2Ab1eNQq0yOb7cry3Q4ZNQGsSruyyQssmRCcyTysNrNi/pO4xHojRxa++s9jt2m/3xXlX5rQYNe2b0f7+ZGIQDdUFVjeLZa2Rd4/KmeFUPAodt1fCRzdIXzFA31eBmaWzbqrLEnMO++fBczir8/aZwX6kSeABMy9Lgex+J0vyNTcQ8j/adVOtFX3OAqkKQCY6zdhVE68MnkQ1YFkKmS+wIjHDSHWxCKx3QCzA1B2p2Rn+/9YraA3LRWi9wMDEoIrpJrX6G2py65J9YH48fmiMim8cNHd3XlV/o/qHF/J5DxxcwF1SyeY9nYDBWv61DHnBehCeFDVzGuWs0jsxuD27kjKOTPIEJIB7C8HSbEAGVOxcm2E+IAEDEUVesgUFpWKL6KOwctWEO0YprlB/4lvxvHExOOm3qLExxl5Jfxc/u+5/2nKSCdmdb28VfSRyUmeIEuSa1wV3ResKgu6eA/7FPETptCu29WM0UjEeu0gQNoVBSlJmpUrxdWNG6mIeZSyqZmiiaWY+Mcg9W8e/aIaAbKZGb7ni1wO9y2ytYoH4nwI9dM2pZ/LOM9GfnlnK9e/Tpz4Mzk5o3qXQg5cqX3gf5P0SSzlFWDjd2PyDsBRawF6vri1yR6cMC1lJY0C7tXWEUsaloI4zC7RfOwuEk/Hy51uIJ0PTf0PGPb/3RXpoKA+lE+4c2HXNpopaHMgFOtDUiK6Q0XglVJdNDu4JGzeiVE5mOmg108V0C309MxLuRUA6mWlE2dw8BeCA2EG00w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20010","langCode":"vi","question":"SlfAq0Q46Qi4Zr8KO9oby5ioj3/sMAhwAoiUC+joLTbWNxKhmU3HiA0v5zoRHR37NKECzFZe3p964QoXPxfUi3epukRZBm6Nexx0jO2N464\u003d","answers":["more well","as well","not as well","well"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE0CyFjgdkOTK2SG/BMNBVjm/y9XEZ24vn7wSkmnQBUE9SWbbfHrgqQeGZDJZQTf/Qipe26mcfR7nV71u+7bMqHI+KWgNLf63aG/VqaJFB1lrOPR0JVl5qNn2L1CJ0i7O9074vqvEdjKZmgiFXDUsWZ+k4rAO/noiRn9Rn/zZQwodoPgg7XDE/tSj8+NB7by2BdqD3Pb4cqpl2F7NCoytBg0Xq9MdTOVYX4ma0pn+RHBon4s384wpu1bvbq7mAx9jZ3fOAaKsTlGYMKA32+STiPL1VN6BjzVHgRR9NH4hSmuug0zTRmoimQyDqhfshwfkSqEgpLWQQ3GNAcOUmPe5CqCzhOfxecIJZqMewGDTXb6UU65f/VRWBGySUZpmnU44b86cFOsPgmHEM1ol5fEmyZfkems+HmVzjybiR31+nEv/RJ518IeZYMsr/MzPppzQopBj8DBIExTLyG2YYuKYqjqEUTVUFJAWdn64dsChoT648iGBf+/lxqELngddHcrM7OQG8/mgn8cZPGnw+Eypu4TKHQy/dZNyjiipUaMD+VryL7OLXKQd+V3lFPeJv/i3MoENbmlSWZJLtfbYvlLSgmqxuACVM/k1MGYi/QUvasudXqnP6AYHYv/N72S567fIUE9Ah8qecHeege06DrXEsOC7l+ZI/395Vrnxom8ooRXBKd1f8P6Cd4umg9TYpBfzqQV/IQZXfVKUpS/GzWvN2biDFgKKvnZSl6MAEO/bYJuE7tGfTHTvXW9D7OOADyKhpaVieNTiG2cqDUa/QYSAAnPCKZbI0Ka5vDUv8lGzlpfp"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20011","langCode":"vi","question":"btwx+N6lI7y7HwxbOFNxmIQAHmcdaOlJxtssBQj+7jOpE4IuMGPQTld6vx0hVJUrgmN14LaDv48UovCzHAYcWaY7tG+ZsEqUjfQaoU7dDut+CvrECKvE7ulhZJ+jZO3g","answers":["more quite as easy","quite as easy","quite easy","not quite as easy"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7QKks8Bx8AOEDi3EQp/sqctWqq3okM5E9gL/q+f/PIt8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5NjDCMHj6arpGolXJpEdb3NDmQL3ltLRbzQmHMDghsLE/G7XRyPYlL5zRXWgu/DGoJU6H1eINIGacy7Qqnp2snaAqjJViSd3x2n+gQ/gpBK2+amUxnlG3B6zjeXX4PNSHNEj8X9xQWtNwyyGkOLoFiGgzLuHIR7POBmQrrfHACQ9dYGpD+zZLJugIckFUYY57Ke1kKRWBzNlOGCXKWx3RhA+/QybMUDcHsLM70jXEG03nIwDWUXrsqaspXj8toAMHtMTwDD1BKc3LGrkbdDt0vDlzVTCuLOOEnVugiEgqwKJDh4Ddjcm40gHc+ZJ/MrsQutTnr78/2V3MrB5tMwOS4QP4YfIk9RyPjVBNRQ+H0S4xIm2iGcxv82iVYCGsAJbM6ErKO6MVQvIgJd7+YWuldh9IO0Dpu6OkIQtFhgiprDYoArxYYgudzll7BkpmBrNOEDy6LwD/rIu97Y2z2YCScXEpnucWotfVgVFJsxRFe2TI70rtkCOcDY0PRXA+QpJVSX5LcVggqaEs1/UAeyMYChwzEzMyLotRD0kCCPEOW05eO308G5UBf4SaaY8LJLi7MUTNXoJ41BHuc9F8XaLtuOQmTJ+/8dbriR+MK5g4/MHk7g0/AQRTqyfWS2j4oQIYU+k0xZa2IGdwBD0YQLSlsXj9OByA84lDjsZrjtxZQ2sbnNy+G7W6XCOHFjDCVKCVxNaI290ePLCrqrbskiquqC4InaziAXbwiC047zuw1XVZwy+C9/jcLrCMX49Na3O4sikb612hD5apXDbjT5smeF4zRkr5oJAy1oeciEzfUmTku6h1tyFTQSCmbp0U0kBzfPaIQjhIoGN9Gx4pZ21gox7UgGI/oJAimEDzCc7s3ey1gAtk+k4FwUtkSYzb1GzkFz+/mlWvuwHvXlk7V8Q8T1waDuKWRCsirBjyeXwbUeHGHhJfHIuSzy11BwwiW1xmA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20012","langCode":"vi","question":"SXHuAh/quS4cI3U1SWzM3XHnlktWt5z6T4+T7+5DGQeEywYnDNrlmAWqK/mY3GfZ","answers":["not nearly less comfortable","not comfortable","not nearly as comfortable","not nearly more comfortable"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzh/tgztvALdzlvXzQusknWUEZnm3xZGr2/8peEmhYTPC0a61WfVJ6rHGxoRqHI0N/bWYCHArhcTFkdOgQI2XRPoHomYNtw5to+gzKJC1m6nQpgPMugRRG5h9hKF1xxG4Olb879Vr2RgAe0XH5H23uHIv22QSS8T3JCDk/+BSrJD87ZaTXuDjPcI4MjBb3nuvoR5NU/lY+9eWD3zcvp4WsHivEZGlv9y3DIP99TPVZJSpQDvBmt9i3biYFnclj1RSC9j8jBiZ2qjqu08V2HKMavmE0XXAVH+a3nYVg5/abD3l0YvIDsq4LELN8Vy37L6ijfXDomXxJn3mrvme4GR1VddOnqAUM2im8NoehVS+LK6j/Uk1XztNCk1SLSmsKAjheyilRlxmFscEP76dV6cjaywiCdMlfvlf+XniBNxNaY84e3Z568cxh0/AoFvyxoZRDOFB3NGwkkvIguY7noB5xtbqjIq7kq4y/9k/UGUsyVlP77N6+jRWFh/sHqDXq0auAq7TN+A1ARNAq07AxbbLHoJg2jgNK6B5CF/K3C/QjOpwBJTBGb7I/2axk9xtq63n+0NZSe8EsAeJOHr/rJD/XSd9WJErqWRBMHP8RxKygN5/JagQUtiZnGEQXiJnyb/+wbdMH1nFQ8O2DYjQyOogwXmAOqXC18pnfgHmxBNKCfqa4Xt3bz/KD4UNfyZ5bxI6qkrA76rv35aHNjT0GXBk8Dc2CxwHrdn6akxUAD6OBGw9yaf4d+WDMx8E23r7pmyGaxKNdHqaZpOefwtuoi8JKj7iYbaEfDCLveqt6BM6ZELEKhUjgxYaCX43AVH3+29ARll+ijAJe+juitIA+vUc42RfBEH5vnmBftY5V8Zz5/PWh5nP2A8J3Or3SMPz85nHtBdT7rPUEY4CvfjajdINlBsXG+ovcl01y8gtKS174GPx2Zl7ldlgHEdJKPYTIqqjcXoWPP4YtBmMKj8DNwCFNE\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20013","langCode":"vi","question":"C0SFniuF3axxwron/5ep+Y3JATo0oyLb2zy2YEQledXy55YeHFqlxaagVuxt1ybh3s08t/cZd9OQfbwve9jzMR6TbCTwwyslEvth5rkNemc\u003d","answers":["not more hard","not so hard","not much more hard","not less hard"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEyzJ7OVUxEJ7qqhqO+fejvzIMtVhJHtIfup0q5MszttRtJxsKLIWO8aMJn4Z/9jMil3lyWQ9aJTZ6IsBGGK3dw50/2PfE03F6qUcESKYnYcu+qQw2gZsiSrn/Hdl3p672d17cRMcma2rF+zWY2zrdf+l1kooRO1lhOwjbW0xp5ihN3xPIp4Z/ODrNGSZDzcZ57hhkHk7Lre2kazIqguUsHW3UgOTlI/FeseQ3/37MOzMnIwDWUXrsqaspXj8toAMHh7WI5XhXYqR3TVeOHv99tdg8X54RQlqs9J02busKlWgpKTqwfJZgjJ4ZQ+MKa1oJUm7PaSWJsPmSfjprxTult4shHZP7u7i0GU/qVqaWibFGTTXDKoOZYLDZtCXK+3cQZBUOotFx4Lj3i4KCoFo/dQDCL/mNDkCMNWAtCE1QFoSUsfKXe8+PzTl92hL/tl5HFZeYOUihoUSfpOBgeUdNa0ivAfiXTjzrKxmjOSHfO/zp6HJRLxF7TJJWzIWd/5UTPxWx+m0/FFAWqb1QDlKvkSZ2hCjtWNQJ2ih8i9T6tsoBRlbQ3RHW5RgALGm1+V5C9N3F7KzRCBTcgoINHoR+0D34oAScE5smDGnRaj6eZjO6vVdzcJgLegDxUuIlTwQ/llPE5FQAAc9dHYc/2HQu4nCBW4IVi0I4H2zeITFnQQoxpez10E19JSlAuYpzlizASDZDUkHhe9SbVHzOeO4PwL5XzAfgQoIBWlJIrHJbSa3ohCu2poc6XQ0JKL3rjaf7P632SC0uE3imYTkbpMV82ZIBMAda5J6xRL8GwN6U9Ar8XYu462hxN+TgeGeJu42mw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20014","langCode":"vi","question":"VeQT47/coJseLDUPSYFKQ2ObjjsiEb7fjcnlO0aDjnyjHlJJCeDkG1ROGlHvfvWt","answers":["more","the same","so","as"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6s7Cm0PleB3NkrTCT9/hcYMVr70fG/FxCBCH44nUm2un0oMyJxyDnh87lWRTF37RHZ9CXxb3m2G6T0u26rqsSO2xt41OgqXIto5CV40FRL5T80rMrk6D65VwZkViMIGcKdd57ONfCHx9S3isgzEwAJRI31ghYz+moSGxSyYEQP3RKPa9yEKRyTah/zBK0GuPdPW1EaoCuI/Hd9/uGyF5DM2p1rwW1XazyfAIZuNONuUVXQZz/h9qArQs8+k6jAS67lOFrIaiDOjvJ5RQwsF1hQsrz6gB3WmI76Pts/un3t87r0YMOJ8ZvW6pzq//6E59zCNyPA0lidspja13T2fqrx1Mg+7uBEqRZQTACHkyhLOOjyugHN+eqItpLOoKQXNg9uQfaFRnNnOXDhuQVI+t703fE8inhn84Os0ZJkPNxnnuGGQeTsut7aRrMiqC5SwdSq8+URAgJ6UdRZfX+7MtSb6iYgpWw1X9xbXOewIHsj0gq1OzrXU2ibZkU6aVLK90ZAg9/Cx+LpVfF552ziWvg73PFgzzUExKziRIhMP2sVeTbInvWzQsIZrPPtbYdquUSBiHkKzr8XbZW1tcqVDAg7YuLgRKH3ECOi+0tLYo9GkFy0O+u0ECKoACGu27tFyOslGbHsz8/arAYerwWpS/15wfMWnOOH9ywDaeeaUwKxQ0DirO0B5p5Tw128NNnUCzoxJC2Su7V21sQnIrsHbqkSIlgi/x9CaTbcitA6kAxjOGi4UO5xOxqbNh23JJ5EvPEVAOplpRNncPAXggNhBtNM\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20015","langCode":"vi","question":"E5XIOXuMCpcPtIwxNpgc85eVG1uP/+Q8kRUovey8BksY6tptIwfY5RqZ9QcxG/1p6KMVOzP6NZaA8DePRIFP4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["more","so","less","the same"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6s7Cm0PleB3NkrTCT9/hcYMVr70fG/FxCBCH44nUm2un0oMyJxyDnh87lWRTF37RHZ9CXxb3m2G6T0u26rqsSPnJty0pDmlfylZz+KzkKioKWZ2GsbxsWGz827P8wIz0d4Pe8xizUSdiCQt2zHRa+t9eFlM/qFgjqdlLYwBgaCrszdo9YoqqMfcROwKw7tiQRTBPfctfHPpuZng/Luqaxe0sW9D/Ura+r/RKB4MvVoqgCjQonBw2aUmH7bMSeJ4ZWuN23Bcw0RfopFY+F/DYL415jKXnPrIvTsjlgP+C6RBCak/px8cmgrtXTUJWhAPtOfl0chOWwsDsqOdYBCDwKx7hWVkpnseGVnsGfOaVXKUL8aZNFOrhmbD4AFzD1eV6qRdfgMnI3ktHY7UX6ANUU41NxDyP9p1U60Vfc4CqQpAJjrN2FUTrwyeRDVgWQqZLxYiq2Bz3dJKOhjP9X7hViJ5LG62bw/UmIPCM9m4A055Js1tu6SMIA7ohWC+VyjUN2rCbt4cNYqTDYTrNWIB9lUy8RgyalbGpCRks1PUBY2QMH1P73lGjW6ccdByVkbJ3kjVOncIKvoVzKvgX1AGmXjlecB+x2qSbydytB3myjb+fQLlRVAmojxUCgsy0s8vwL67P1beNMPQIIXLnxL2Xo9PQIfKnnB3noHtOg61xLDgJj6PQw1AP72GXZrmmn2QVfmtgOi66XpqIVvzO5qJLz5aHEu7UIFzSG0mLqXclpYsMaUTe5epl8gK9dD8J+DldrLw6bKlNwctXiuJx+Y3plVyA12yoFcNPb76dMEJlkEzo55GMi6PTN7QPiVloD6V+w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20016","langCode":"vi","question":"e2to/IpzLsx6ADhT691s3uXs512OgcoqB15Va8Gl7zbg83Zr4Nr5F6cPJoq94UWn1XWzBJtxCPSpfjcxXI1DgVSAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d","answers":["more","less","as","the same"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6s7Cm0PleB3NkrTCT9/hcYMVr70fG/FxCBCH44nUm2un0oMyJxyDnh87lWRTF37RHZ9CXxb3m2G6T0u26rqsSMF2kZDqd0mm13bHG63rr0GdsSfwlzAEhsFuzNpgJSjv83zsLcmFeN5nerUuNMcT8hd5clkPWiU2eiLARhit3cOYijGd6/SMzcPEu8cXXv58ve/DwY9gGi05GQxq8hvAJpQ4zynX3Esnryyyu/eB7AOwBUdaSyqaYf4/rSwFZ5gMOQ1LuvwB0l1WNdgreAXW7vFS3IL+6cvpBNSCBQ7SYBE3XtxExyZrasX7NZjbOt1/yQiusJYOlVjXCufEK4puDJth97Frou7F5Q//De926geeexArI2hRPylJS1cQOlsY0fmF3mbGE6BdSUqEQb6/TMxpnRTWKfNG9ElBI32ywnmt7gD2KJvb0YUqU+XqI/QEjiJPOEGmgaQHGUvNTIQQGCxShadSPab4aJGUGhPu4169tkpol45a0FYz5FkvCfHknOX7nuaJevzzSL9UFgKQ7SN/vJuysWZ+9KLYLu1/lydro56+xnjCtXVNnWpCvfCuhpIToJ0eus872+J2qbWhMo15R2hInBZpiNyjVUen0Egw/jCeLSL/S125jkYuEXE9Trk6z3AgKWvD4kc8hadnDq9q1HQZxkT03daiars3FNtm/ifNd8sqFwQFpAalIJuviAFM6n7r0Fo+aK001pY6kWnDThEA/x12KNEV4ddfqj0CVVizbX7paiW5tZc2VogBi+bgt9ue/I0IfLerFQx+mlfsSW/PgLNirhI0zUUMOmb"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20017","langCode":"vi","question":"qFeax0OSNIHSrN2wOk1Kb/VxGOnSv+nD/U2wqv3GtvaK2JbEXOKTahsHbURwIIWC0QpDMlLmyOJLORfZuq4wsQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["fast","as fast","faster","fastest"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5PTDQrRwdGZ1BwcH7zgealGjyZt2IFDpDzzFPMaSE8bZyPmFKJp0PTwYrMOLU0gczyK5qkUidUsoW76Gh80yxLhw7RXmhQhfGrnowoj5BpWHqbBFGHV8hTZG9HC1z2BlmxDRcpYq+E7sPCJ+4PB83CNNyMj+L4PeWSIcHM6NbmGn91FCnmH+A8+YbE+ygUVfx5fsFUm32nHKJttNJVzfKPsJHNFgPQTLjnmzuc+yJpqELTWFyT5ty6DHvLkQSwGivR298LDucfTVQOvK9QFCqeGIJx5HuseoAs83Rqd4RKISyT5pHAK63wSM7Hx3+mjVxVKTyn3gPlcF5CaXRHRKgcQfufwEm7+BoqCofIjPII3Lju1ln+O561lxn1+osgI/KKVvcZdqfqjQNvQ5O3enNQwK0ChLtyT2h436uaXeO2DvzImjrlHXm72TMvjMFRqLKJmVnalwyS3EGaP+Rod3kR5LQQCk6eFo/uLrvUHilSPKbfQKoUzsTIxqnMbEh8oWiK8B+JdOPOsrGaM5Id87/NHLdrfwsl/HjATseuoa1r0Y6ZubkRynTqwcJAYqWprDG5zcvhu1ulwjhxYwwlSglf570iet2bYj7zuipihais5RSfFLBNQ7wzROZdMuno4ZO6D1V9BsNKVF4braXaUzn36QAfc31d0i7rZxheejOV1ML1ie4n75OQ9pVq5OOCmKYR7c72kDmG5I3fiE/8Z/wGstUuRifT6Zq6Uur2ITbR05aRy4Hrt7fwkK/klQh0Npg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20018","langCode":"vi","question":"rp0zmrt4WbSBQmcXGoaIN7ccKO8MJbgc6e52NfsQdnLl4ocES8JxvOA/cjFuvalXvjsVNh8nrgpIESkoqRIBOnuucVgUxxkm3PkZVlP7/5E\u003d","answers":["earlier","as early","earliest","early"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE66qJiyi01D/ZRL9PFw2V/J/sM1C12ui009lzqenLiWiF9zcXsHCalYAfN9cBN4youipfI9Zc/oDUb8TORvzXARSf1Br2YgFVgvDf14O2ZR25CCtZz0szPzYVI+YKtHuAwV0HEqJ7sSHjzv0+YRMABn3qWjZez7Bp1tsC9v5PGUGZSls+FsDLh3V3Knvlo9y1ISANJOcmn8bhN+Z0/OmhdbZZxgM0t5gcsSbilffun+UaM5bI4sR+btGuyKUfcl4o2LOPD8bVgfswUhcSwrtnn6YM124DewtjjgvOu5KAHM2XfKlmr7ORcZk1xJCBzTgYFrC93pJQYQwTim1Qzvz1rQJDZG1OJAHADz5Boq4DeEtWTFVXg9i8v5YG1qPBFgoU9IvGfxkFwhw6ePEx/i8whVhDNsUL9IuyU59UG4MNVrSBqM6tBJOFsTHT+LSNlPIq3yLVzAqRSS2TnI5p/VAgv5N5hnEvCgHiEW/C+kk1VYnNeUdoSJwWaYjco1VHp9BID9ppYKTwYZD8Vp99wHyBFvJRmx7M/P2qwGHq8FqUv9ecHzFpzjh/csA2nnmlMCsUIizqPtre0mfz+hlViiSOH7Gjz7332aOH4BE5TC5AeWkoL3cIYhr7mGTkb54UrfzIqYOt9PVPsCC2XIOY+ti9PcNsPHZSnmvNADMh20f6Qd/xU06ZC1QSywudFQD9jE4k4c/H14ebWIdOpPV2KXTP/Q\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20019","langCode":"vi","question":"GboPKSXjE2VXtdqOhXjWBVFzYPv4GOlOAO8Bs4Tcy7lUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["interested","more interested","most interested","as interested"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzLOZSs0HbE2ATgZELJCimOc5BO4Agu5x0byISv9ybMkycXNvGQdH3VhYN9MYTQDBypMA3iTB5F0eYsm6OvlTeT7adVEtssnur4rbv0uMjn0pPzvY1t5jVIB28R0q1cMMBVZqJmqVz9mL4mryjUW39ihV4Jh8Yc4w53HsNdjnucs1+scZyOpcZheN4Y5rOuLqTdnzPr13E57NFu32NS16eCd+oCRIAj/3xGyF03z/tpXvgRQcLp54wF9tju9JnxG8nDa5+MMG8aN0YtmgAxYF08RIgeqYVHxdAtppIvTbujHqnuafqDD3fqean5yyzfj/JnoI9UxZcJm43mK69W8tffFD4kj3a91th8wygh67P20//o1p3wIZrC9SmDEUPh/rXktBAKTp4Wj+4uu9QeKVI8pt9AqhTOxMjGqcxsSHyhaIrwH4l0486ysZozkh3zv80ct2t/CyX8eMBOx66hrWvSwYpuSNvwXZ1Z3xbtdLtVCN9yTVj5l98nU1UaRa0Q/FCXXVY8Hem7Ca2jycAEPGvlwq1X3zicWkqbhVbbFKXwMpz0dmRx06Cgc1jQDGAEjVtKtR6+LkAfht4G4pdWIvz7nv4i7H+wjFYGxWSvlUwssO9A6XC//OiWFi1YcGpwPNDVYhNFaWDk5WJusD5vYg9oZEZN1p/OyTfZfFLBriqh/"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20020","langCode":"vi","question":"lsZ8fOYMMVKZ/KEJEdG7eiIcOw2GYgtA1qW+nMpTn627Wbk5iAVQPVtzCsmT8QIx1u1T9nxIlijmLwOtmp2b/G/tTV7hVcHYXIvP6i/nq+s\u003d","answers":["popularer","as popular","popular","less popular"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9kMtZ1uEcTYXg5+ctoQ/8YKPKXPWZpeMXpnQ+uYy8Ne4y68CbEGopGJU2TTz3+a6NUKiI6GLelsMrpswG3HtRd5A93FWRSVD9s/tBzGLkL6HqbBFGHV8hTZG9HC1z2BlmxDRcpYq+E7sPCJ+4PB83CNNyMj+L4PeWSIcHM6NbmGn91FCnmH+A8+YbE+ygUVfx5fsFUm32nHKJttNJVzfKPsJHNFgPQTLjnmzuc+yJpqELTWFyT5ty6DHvLkQSwGivR298LDucfTVQOvK9QFCqfZMpvZJMESkGQl54fvfRH0ky8VzN22z+5qAUkf2ne/HYal4DqoHU7GzVMU3Rf/kLLJgLDA/d46/jBmXPYJfuBDNaJvkcrOgn6P1s+suUZo9VkPeURcqAcgMxdOzgYA9DAoY1w7GR3rQEAVmclUnzVw5Abz+aCfxxk8afD4TKm7hPuI0LhU9saPbUFm57lrvnCbx16e9NYna3+lXdTMbE4bCdoI92sNeECrtz7Vd3WQHuABMNPru2/fHb8j5i+jCgaH+G/jYHLHNZItsdGLkSvpH9rBxpNB5ayKEoKqomV7xeQ78xHz4Pg5XMu0VDS6tkbpbSAHCPwenP4ltlI/nbAGk/xWr/M5ZzJqyTdLy8sL/h60ihCumQM+nfAn3bfewF2Lm/okykzORvwkYC2dcslP9SZM8q60qhlZJHrvwBDG0uMMtumLdJrP8AgsIhvlNnBwe7phXf6sUmCELoWGc2XC"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20021","langCode":"vi","question":"QUxR+rPZHzeYEHWKyvGbNg4ylvw6BtS9T7D1ABsiXcOptlCWtySNodM6l7ZfiqlTSWjLwQFL9Oz2n18eriYD6g\u003d\u003d","answers":["as clever","clever","cleverer","more cleverer"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwJdR8i1u8G76fi3CuNI04pA96WAnn0kNO9TxtafMR2K1b0jZpJPGEnFIKpLBkgzqPH30t/Ny9KAwZ5S0fN8dxyzN2j1iiqox9xE7ArDu2JB/kRVvO4IW5AcRYRyM3B5/grfw+rruusfkag2ghFkr9GP9STVfO00KTVItKawoCOFfN4/2L5gkZyJU2iAuU1XUKEcy0oiSp7DicDxWeph88XtvDHfmQeKF5+uI8DL0cZdwhDfz90KVOefskhAZsxrmf43EqweHMGAArJVIoEChvXy1RjLhflIJnuqaHD8rQxGQec/pXeGkT9s+5fCxGICvtVVzm0S7c2t1O5CFLeJEDtz/sJcp5lnTV7aSIB57/UOMv59scDI6u8Se8Gk5AdJHeJdTZhGbJbG9tyZEeUHCRvUJHOWFTe3Q54G/C4YpfxPq5y6NMVFAm3pOrjG0pdA4dKTXDO+dL3/n5PcFyiR9nziYL8sxgeAQnr/8ESCDnTtxbCFwJuVp0zZ4mKW0XowFaxKNdHqaZpOefwtuoi8JKj34oAScE5smDGnRaj6eZjO6vVdzcJgLegDxUuIlTwQ/llPE5FQAAc9dHYc/2HQu4mNIy2lBmw8v0i1quKoCza+VAJFx7RuxHN0yXuHwz3OHbSr4tJj6EJXZDeQdIgi1lTIqlv9lJgzfz7zKBB+qmNgFJEj1eA8WISYAcQMuIXWlfY7mhff0sJ3B7Irt4SVlJsYoG009evpQeeWPDl5lHEQQrse87eOx0n6YM0vQGk1RVViJnPpApKI4MPwasXU4oxAlUK1AfvacWbTcixpS5hg3Ymn/J/NC4DSReKz+Bv0H3IivOOQm9dsrKpEDbv+tOVyD63lUdnSDzLtgO/aZsq6KE9iZEOSOvPgVW0GSzFV9KQQIbIaHIce4NuzpqLIad8Ai4yKqm1pfOB4YuVp/dkd"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20022","langCode":"vi","question":"6F2xudbDGgcyKbNmjkfFermILtxMidCtZpgTmFWP3veKdDHaKMLj+i4ls/+qp6Qa","answers":["narrower","as narrow","more narrower","narrow"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE1pf0vymPZiXM1MGXQYuTUdA96WAnn0kNO9TxtafMR2K1b0jZpJPGEnFIKpLBkgzqPH30t/Ny9KAwZ5S0fN8dxyzN2j1iiqox9xE7ArDu2JB/kRVvO4IW5AcRYRyM3B5/grfw+rruusfkag2ghFkr9GP9STVfO00KTVItKawoCOFfN4/2L5gkZyJU2iAuU1XUKEcy0oiSp7DicDxWeph88XtvDHfmQeKF5+uI8DL0cZdwhDfz90KVOefskhAZsxrmenV5cZTuBxlEqj+d78t+7Xy1RjLhflIJnuqaHD8rQxGQec/pXeGkT9s+5fCxGICvtVVzm0S7c2t1O5CFLeJEDtz/sJcp5lnTV7aSIB57/UOMv59scDI6u8Se8Gk5AdJHeJdTZhGbJbG9tyZEeUHCRvUJHOWFTe3Q54G/C4YpfxPq5y6NMVFAm3pOrjG0pdA4dKTXDO+dL3/n5PcFyiR9nyk/j4F84VDrHg9U0ZfxDerxKshlzi6ZJFpwksk0PfINqxKNdHqaZpOefwtuoi8JKj34oAScE5smDGnRaj6eZjO6vVdzcJgLegDxUuIlTwQ/llPE5FQAAc9dHYc/2HQu4kLr0NxDH4OCFSea1lAfOuQmDN3F0RgMXM1Orsdinm5I0IvbWoYotLZRx647WR/RVIBfP9G5NTy5jQD2xXj7Az9gxLPolmwNxNfflXigSP/MtXndjd4M6542co7AAuYEGgctSh3Jc6KzheYepOWatShW0gAoDAruhEuTpPUw2FfWbCabdoBExafef8fu9JFin9U+BolaXtcvg+5mBPywI8zF0gPcBZ5Z01PFoR78d/dfcwht2aZ/8Wil8AOPip7tqX2BcClDCXBnux0IkGtmv9aO4BZpVfYd9MDofPyNAMsHC/zv+NIC58glPuN0D2r4jpz/gc4FczL4aZAKl6TH1Mn"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20023","langCode":"vi","question":"2syYKxQVl+XZ2x434/9FfokKvLVUI5TEAlyVRFZPkjaY7N9p1C8glw5QFZBoctT5Tms0DB2IOPtn60youexQxA\u003d\u003d","answers":["as useful","useful","more useful","usefuler"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEw1OqLWLB2PN6zyQRnZPzpf5NhwmK3t1loF/G2VuShRbIb/MZ9I3iB0NPbXSdnnN8s3zsLcmFeN5nerUuNMcT8g1SmJq3l9yLj9giOcWJY6yzSjMXr6P95p46Ccd/G36eWpbmfBG+0a/3lPFj7Rvdep/qYVsr8uxYjs55s2TWLQoZmxRYTUbQTVmpB8/GNySfszdRh4KOaGyj2Slw337C6QmzzcmCj/3CVe63gU1eNT1TG2dXw/8gEULHoCGLiT2wewkc0WA9BMuOebO5z7ImmrE92BINmpU0SofcLa/+LzS9k4HquDPIW6Kaa1rrm1Fia8HyVmbozI62B4NxASiWPUVZJiIYb0seB2dKTaAaUzA5ZJY2Men7IMe4LIMDpH612z5O6+glIgjWr5gBvu5GMJAlUK1AfvacWbTcixpS5hgIEdnV9joQ8nPQ/79iPbw3FIXD/q1bwuDaILZEPmpaCGbl8H/VjYMOTOf23C+zd1hrn+qDkdZ8OzKGVEk6n2C9tLjxgZWowmIQERHulade1XAXq+uLXJHpwwLWUljQLu1dYRSxqWgjjMLtF87C4ST8b/Djv51pmFBvLNPgDcljW5bsQb4pm4GkxnVY3+QJIaMglYjfhThhPTI1OUFn0W/B5dLrNrueBCHafgPKKWBt+yIKeNG/5qN4Zu2B3qNLtefUpT+tLa7z5hbRaXbw43+WdhRZ5QTsxMZcaAJ5W35mto\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20024","langCode":"vi","question":"HQ+NDo+pSphoKu3ol6h49/3U0sddyh9CrvuWsVEpofYE7E2MCEyVJW+DIima9dCp","answers":["as patient","patienter","patient as","more patient"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEySxzCOhWedxg5/wTkp8tj8nLJyORi5ofPbTY2PlANC9E7dDiInhECPmVMtAIx1oeoJZUk2+wSiynFAUeFTBJS/TSrnZEY9VmrOVP4ECYPnhpkA+pzNdmFl+zh4UNUlNSTTrPvw+HNU9OnUS/GMh/wVvCmWEdCNnXc5aNAgXqDcT++XbKj1GPYfDqCi8Gnflr5avu3y+gcwzXJ0aC8tgAHkoZ6xm5KqnC2SYEvZbhi/Nbfw3UsmsrZ9whFJlTGf6j0xJBzsSWoRPwNZC2ZeCL9/Io+QBzOznp+cYBLmMd5hgbWGtxI5sB2N1oEw8YSc+fzKkW7drQYX5s6kGnB6UWnZXhCRlBlpmVwQqgDoXE1EMFgF66tAxHwEGsBMM6DuaixVo5LXKLSpiuM8qAvFlMl1MSQc7ElqET8DWQtmXgi/f3F5OBvRRLatsEpUxp+VdDKnxaQq8N38UBYmyumCTz73jnjA7oYQAhrJHZ2B4ZFWkDsROByaP0gN/i2T4nAT2ol17XjPM8bMwzLWkYk+oxTywSYsihjlEF25W9GR878SgxJTSy0zku7P3/lTOShQeIJ2HtH3XZ8ny3Vkkyy/PDNtJExChHcqmpT9NtudDKGXebnNy+G7W6XCOHFjDCVKCVxknfA+DsMbrdugHchJNJ6REMb+r1TOJgErfYovfxB9JD01vjrm/WfLJII6waQ0SzOeE7EryAQ9sgRdcYX40BORGassh0Ot2CI//Zk5/o2KoVIRlb7T3O03JrprNLs7wcrhd3zTVy2uOeFRz2S+b5CFP4r9LGBpbluJJsZTrwRhqIyNTXLB5w4SGRxpJKEMSsXj1C/A44j1aWg7uTY0wMiikAtvaadu5HF8oqArQhJ53n45mf6910hllOaZmDBhal1DkFH/K+zlJXsH8azdozq3HnJPOKTezhA+RVZasQBJqjHqSz5j/dxT4+nZMaAO189pL3Lue14acX3EER6YUhiETMQD/4FjpnFBSBe+f9D0iGnkNZXkkNbUuG7SaUj1MgR/Ms80Ufkku+CAqvwCMjLk\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20025","langCode":"vi","question":"OPmpB8PUvTkNIJTBkM1hY8RSK9M7A0MPRc0+B18Oj+S1WVtnsryhk929trtQdc/t","answers":["less long holiday","longer holiday","more long holiday","long holiday"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7vysWERNE5OCv671V5GaJrYwuz+v9oXiOXGWjnrcB/Mn0oMyJxyDnh87lWRTF37RD2pB7XUbtaqsELKm7Y9EKLNKMxevo/3mnjoJx38bfp5aluZ8Eb7Rr/eU8WPtG916n+phWyvy7FiOznmzZNYtChmbFFhNRtBNWakHz8Y3JJ+zN1GHgo5obKPZKXDffsLpCbPNyYKP/cJV7reBTV41PVMbZ1fD/yARQsegIYuJPbB7CRzRYD0Ey455s7nPsiaatsvPdl20i4q2XWuMO44dASK23soLN3PhsWpLuksqvm0ZxG45VI5qTLrFHF3cl5MaRVkmIhhvSx4HZ0pNoBpTMBsWQU18jSj4zX46aQP9fAiVWImc+kCkojgw/BqxdTijECVQrUB+9pxZtNyLGlLmGBvNISzGo2iYzVHgUYtxsUzEOmIEMM6FgVd6Uc3WhnDsrQrVeKkqKK6wrYuuwA/rQVc+GB5U5ZYcn9+Zzb4PBBZC9WYFREaUBoBTYs3V2UGrKPeP5t48Xfcz5t1npyi6pNsboxZewjlqX/RSTwLVsz12DY6byUbF2K5py7PJJIXb8Yfr42/PXhs32WwMa6KzLdIDuIticGiMeEmE5ZLu4zhu4TrHXRUHJqtifC7uon+83aIEQEWjXEgJjaFxFUmBkNZpTw9pCXM/fY4Sfn0uNbign2nuLSxc6yAUAVmyL11tA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20026","langCode":"vi","question":"E1iaX/uaviGyeO4utCNq//4z+7H2AasoUn778vBqA+ziSTIJV+WAHuGrJ3+twzSAnSlWnsNKxRVKJqn7xu3BmtYGC6yHHYZ5tWqcdNVKWGvb6EA2etK9FEaVzWacsH7raKp4CbibjCiYhDRHsJdfZg\u003d\u003d","answers":["faster","fast","as fast","fastest"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/pbS22tHF0BLGA3VpaVjS3H8qqR4KblCli4jDD+VALkZqe+MnLWQKKhwrY53/nHPacCl0DDWHPjUrltBY+Rqqee26KPehHM4ejirUBBfSmT0a6sDHUeHkA7XAOVsK0DB4TPTVVP72gU5O+M1qSAIiJ1HmLTLLzn8n0cZUFoSeXJeVqBpta2C5n1w3Z3G8zquDUJx7UV42ESkvCp7AYNIKxUth/hN2xDmgjRH/8iZsbwE+K9VWsDjbal7tTv0IzNGx+cutFs05BotVXpUWfNJjZkMArvY68uBWVNN5izXppe4ruHEdpqW6hei5Tihx2+lHE3nLhX5AnRb7XUjk+X5RofnLrRbNOQaLVV6VFnzSY2xMiyTEdw2sZKKkfj37mfxPTNoWf/l9IFqlfGh6vv+M/lp2586lE05Ji/qw9xXpKPN6y9KGCpmWnK0zrNoKOKbYEkhU6UIeuAEFsk+tGLKdhvN0sbipdPlJdIoNcSsZUvj22AsOny6jp+4VgLZaxnvN+pVgFfOy+E2v/j9bJ8SPmZL/76inZcZt8BjfzWIGsxIBnMOSMLqxZVbQQnFio+b/9rQ/C0dt7YmXs4mK9Vu7vWMwGJIESFKsqjuvZicG2Zrn+qDkdZ8OzKGVEk6n2C9tLjxgZWowmIQERHulade1XAXq+uLXJHpwwLWUljQLu1dYRSxqWgjjMLtF87C4ST8cVGmU4+zvMAKkrQYTVLaVr3sazksB3+MqnxleJIHpq43sZXaR0ezXTtAjvBMAqc3HMzHy1swAaiY9EczLCpNWQuiRO4l4dVln8QpC6VLD/XoAEufrh351XeiK/HSX4e6NNI0RXXizO4An7u1UNeuxgwheS8jAXaCK/BezBNc5GvvPNQtwR+ALk93GA2vAdfzw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20027","langCode":"vi","question":"fzOHhEUVpQusQ6gTomN3YGV486s+ZE/NykUPM1B52k9i0aqrmVfg1Zfk/0YclPYw5vk+NhIJupUmsVedT8ms+g\u003d\u003d","answers":["frightening","more frightening","most frightening","as frightening"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6A2kCnh7gVFu7RqXWVCBne50Zo9zJnnZOSYX8A7A3eaEyN8wH4nF+VyHorBUJeaIpSgoi5rMgRmAycqPpjr75WYG+TtAGY1dxXvReQNdqwSAlZFI0R5DftP+MpOcMEgpgpYSPAGj0rg+nTzzhJxEDIepsEUYdXyFNkb0cLXPYGWbENFylir4Tuw8In7g8HzcHO39OyKV9anN/4Ri9XDRqX7F6EqGK/dz9OVpCrlJT2hijvnVu5w9lBrlo4WzenpNufX8J36KKCl/8h8sICyLtXKyvAGWitFSybfnPzcm0i2luVsJ7Irk/JaHIPiSF7+0VTPAV2J6osVoyLlgp3wtNaIthI3I/FVWo1TfDe5vqVOjROmdJopeLNBfg5pwBaRd7sYECfFZ5ROWU6Ar87aTpab7FoyhB0spDcqUEJT4Lek55/Xk4HX8AsK0xUhrW1gZtWlTh3XZRRVORU2ihiLpgAMYkgrp1x29DGbcPyNY8Q2FWSYiGG9LHgdnSk2gGlMwLsBMyZPIcskOoyi1VKAA7ZCJnZzlgpVnjQ33uSGGedtG1zy8kMwXq0A13zaj+XlaW+0TM1OgMud4mHjDnk5p1F4WEX8i9heX/OPt6cuPoL7H0PlPQZHZbUP0ZIuOvhyLoENbmlSWZJLtfbYvlLSgmqxuACVM/k1MGYi/QUvasudwbAao1106z8CW9X5GbgU7Ng2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF28HC8KbGUypAl+QLpNSixlhLtkCof2MT2ecD2E41BeVa42shFYpeJpWd615FU8QkCtMuRvRIs2RQKt4yzsxBjeJG/Vtb0xauTNP2gKoBIZpAorrwFn65jxLhNUANcKylWk\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20028","langCode":"vi","question":"cOFqG7F0PmARLzWgr5jj+OqBmEXEF1Mw/uo9UrFJjo4n9jdp783dyfWB5RJVbfZoJ2fcGkVPpjGfc58NC2BnpclDsXYaQenPugxhHnWtw/c\u003d","answers":["taller skyscraper","as tall skyscraper","tall skyscraper","tallest skyscraper"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+WyywacWrm1N/IIKIgF/Qg7NZlAdoNwYgm453mc8XMwXPgI1xpfTdN+WfNyeg+Zq+0XSrAJB0p5T53o0V/1UzsLP+ZmnO7joviM/vHJRfsU+dEIdFV7tdOwyzJZ7RsNyW6y48LyZOSQOOdHBrtQpvOk/O9jW3mNUgHbxHSrVwwwFVmomapXP2YviavKNRbf2OtoIOdA2PsLUFzvOE9MN/7RrqwMdR4eQDtcA5WwrQMHe2+mc6OrrlsMCC9NgKdkKmrv2ZlV93eFnbyMLNdUJw9KQOeqnlCmVoJ2WF0Km7yUfjjm8bpTmYvyyJFKU5TjKJp83BwQpgVNKKQwufvRJiqN0lay69jNYiG5s6jCSEM0SkDnqp5QplaCdlhdCpu8lDdwqIhki+illtsEPKLw5cFwiMpduYVzh/VAC76eslcgvN89ucTSNe2zG8ScjrZ2LdNOtFjgJCE0JidlQ0eBlMT36uNEsXYfroR7Flyv5/KftQdAOFe/lovvG70JkVa+nhKNAK7LnvPtePPZmOVBvRN9cCTuOz1i8UIDha1Q3HbNq5y6NMVFAm3pOrjG0pdA4UvgPC8poQMdj/013Altb3q6pcizKInjww4+dqm49X7cMFwwxBdnfFX9c5lgrPiAtjXlHaEicFmmI3KNVR6fQSAolpy0n9Gc5vHIE0Mk3unoh/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8XNKKR/LcnaeMWQhD0nH4PvAvTrCWgg/9kPCt3hqj45C+4PZzpI2jkecQAmnAjgnZ/3apoULT3Ct5a0IlOyoolNCmeg0jsyiVdCYDpQykB+ogJ+UJewuf0TJ7P7+hGvtPmvmbtuh0kC/5kLRkbC+CitH/aIfjwsIap7bUgjac48YQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20029","langCode":"vi","question":"AG+g9uZ3DcwiCSRRm+a1cotaIYCd23HjIG7TrfEzhwMVnqJEH1fGHrEwictJeAcARH45oBSoSrp7AavYJDEpTNnDwpCvDDJcFqzU4lxz5LA\u003d","answers":["older/younger","oldest/youngest","old/younger","old/young"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8SO5SYrar06OMDYJzHE0hpKiKkxUF0aPsRvwF4oJSPJqvEqFo1/hs2NAlgY1VZ8eOxlguH9zpaFi24wN2BH8wnoAb4PRzHzI1KfcIqS3aPWbCTfWXonLkN7XsgviVWNBe+Qn18tsA0fEzKNBamZcYO9nZOCj3z4qKq9394OYAVZprptlgBPxqbrhtx7YJs0oTsHO+GsErNTelWWcz8urVClhIzGRaCN+A43QnF/mu28WRfj3VpjezI+OYflzA8VBnQATexPUnUUJ1x9nERprT2AavEyHC1jx4A5HQXZUQtmUnS+ppLQOGMH5C53vOT65m3w517/rhXGzFALQHWZXMU2jOqpUGf14MxnbmNZ3SEygGrxMhwtY8eAOR0F2VELZmsL9uM5qUvS3pAvnhKOoyd6z0/NIzueXxsO3FTJrd8Pv2KjSp7ytZ0sUgmTT+zT84G0UW81cGaLdmcQKOtuhL1EHQTlN0RItWGBc3urGaXM9pUgslsb0gOd2+3HeNNm6Vk5ksD/AHxE0ke8Irktx4Pcdq4SGaPXXIdV2pbhyTqqhoMgSSMMcR28Vu3PrP8yKcHc/cdOp4oCq/g0krYs3N2Z2hCjtWNQJ2ih8i9T6tsoliuodAO14P5Czh+m4ggDDXU0CtN5o9uG04YuHaxeUnmuf6oOR1nw7MoZUSTqfYL2jDo8CRMhLB6kIj5yR/Y4ZfLjZ2y64pmsmfeStTRuF1ld18uTke3XzV5N4lc1nxRAftvKfH71EkqRnIukGhGPbVxxbT3v57NzhLjjYDBHMBUDGOQJZcJx+TZtEr7bWR2z2zsAih73Rs2rSmvXWe8yC2KqOrut0qTTmqGjAshidEGrvKDQOJR5Vy3r99PJ98+0/JQKU7z6xkV6/80D1V0fSg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20030","langCode":"vi","question":"+GmkKOYBURlxXXjsyu9t42t6oLrVixmcXL0O89UNPyZf0QCuiAk1SR/x97EBfMP3","answers":["worst play","bad play","as bad play","worse play"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE36jsKaPiz4w0L9L4iyZAW1qgveshroluK95/JifLLl5xD3VJGk3wMw0M+SSmGR3VXyDCQ1LtkdQx3DtffmjIIF+giPGRwQbPRvc1lu/EsWdDc46oDA65O48+J3NB5+laFCy8ur0t9/poGOzOkobFEFrlOR2H/oJ4XrPdrP46fBWoT3PMCyF5/URB0udoEuiWvBgGA3zPCcVuDFLbKkuMkBC08lJlzKEgZ5XLtpDopVEofT6IiSI0jViEgK6uUaQkXBBLpSijCcnowDK6Eysb1BWPOCKy40Z0JxvqRysj2RtcYdWrZwkAok4i2A3sRNU6gUUFa14sI+gc5NcDiTEn4RNN7AnKW7z4B0QHnT6sbn+vP0fIe37FRCPWPAu19FKiqggiVT2ah1nFarp3qNhtc3iXU2YRmyWxvbcmRHlBwkbMGeTepIbl6fNJF9GpWbSOK7Au5irY+r1n3BdfrCIYI3RfYCLY+sJwbPBzdvLFSZaiL67TFK1AdcRdp44jTuIel6Unx3gPy2mSlaiUglwUU5JPXQvNfj+aTwPDCulW9UgRuznMqPDKV+ECr9NgESZCDXlHaEicFmmI3KNVR6fQSAolpy0n9Gc5vHIE0Mk3unoh/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8XAB+38nw2UsxHQ1ktUJTDNBw2mtchPaRrBUxOq6XyESViW8nmHFNW1rYqtWsxMcPf9aIA/82g08nFTAeeQUbY5RYVb6mn2x881pIoCFLU+uA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20031","langCode":"vi","question":"RBu6gnu3xSRNLvESZi5IpWB3lkRv7l/6Y5UsxQBVrkz+g/dft260EJNd1IYwfj27/aNm7w71zD4G2V3xKs0Caw\u003d\u003d","answers":["further planet","more far planet","far planet","furthest planet"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEyL5rvNSr/l3X8IKr9bSvSzIgHJ6A7L6AsncLZ/aLJRf/Y9JrQThDwKnD3PGiNK6j2TzpWp0amF0lxaoHKYFR1lsJN9ZeicuQ3teyC+JVY0F75CfXy2wDR8TMo0FqZlxg72dk4KPfPioqr3f3g5gBVmmum2WAE/GpuuG3HtgmzShOwc74awSs1N6VZZzPy6tUKWEjMZFoI34DjdCcX+a7bxZF+PdWmN7Mj45h+XMDxUGdABN7E9SdRQnXH2cRGmtPYBq8TIcLWPHgDkdBdlRC2ZSdL6mktA4YwfkLne85PrmbfDnXv+uFcbMUAtAdZlcxTaM6qlQZ/XgzGduY1ndITKAavEyHC1jx4A5HQXZUQtmawv24zmpS9LekC+eEo6jJxicF781XdBfNptrdKOrcm+AG8e65G2LuY2iX4ix1NYge+7pWK+m2YgdG6zSzq6oj78ySyK3MTEZDqmwqijtqtc4RgqEZ4jvvLNyr39f0Qyk/qgP92OVMobl8S/K/uzuQm/OKZn1geFIT+Te20H03RErBVNoL+j1HphU7NvpygiUbMwGRnUxNJ1AGVGo4fxrF6X1hAUclj7/zLLYpDksne9EEStHJrgAKRD/k9pxNXAZvzImjrlHXm72TMvjMFRqLNfteE72V4G+y82KC2rFXbPcdq4SGaPXXIdV2pbhyTqqKnnPC7h12eLuA1AMHwEqlyotk1wNWZo0EJwDYCUNNrINjtVs+Ij97JvQyctc+ES8dJisd5NqAYNipMTkIs7qyPX+r9TZyKuWr6ySkXbYwXvW0tScnEJQhSFiFHIeETJBPiOzzVH41o2cCfGDtVpsFer1Xc3CYC3oA8VLiJU8EP5ZTxORUAAHPXR2HP9h0LuJW5rCcwTR1dp6zeg0JG/jdkbkT+oCKBG527wFjxAl6EBHHEsl+3r+O0/98Dva5XzMfq4I3XdJbsBwXASHfmx6L8+9pWQomNh/s3CSBsOewmfSmubBZfK+HtCvzmdU4bpGBLEkr+hLBGbN8j8cv2LuTQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20032","langCode":"vi","question":"0pjTQrRPFC9ZsQsr4OCiSb9Zo6xUwW8myojIzqWW/myOwtNh2x51Csxdm8voSkkbVofPMQ2ezyi1DdB8kGV7mw\u003d\u003d","answers":["bigger","more big","the biggest","the bigger"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwEkpiRzuhq9PnkhB5/xzjMvF8kCknQCS72MAKfqi8ZULA6aR8ZMbPx5fAUFPKfprfK7O4Z1spf5MlUFteMMMdrLfzOkX4nRAHB/Af9zKoyNYjDbvJ/dN1th4lmzDkUA/tMh4EzmDsNp1ri4PmqZYCAT8J/n8mKVc2gdDG8YJAXGwFHRvUSObBp8sdA1kuhdnxCUq4vlPQdoRuUDpAQu5lusfMlTevbbJ1RzelTUbOwd7hvsLZ55ocolLt9Pcc/QPqTyURjjEih6Cw+Iez3BOWNoAxpAtis38LrmXmTlQMFa7lpX/efipkEjPKG2+wUU0GXc/6hCvZG4qyxDAjbYXID4Z+LARC9uGYd2J5U5/efcFXJ6P+nV3T0ZAtWcfS5S9CzQUE8y6Ptl7dseoS4Dqlf8VsfptPxRQFqm9UA5Sr5EUBmWJsK90wPpSddJpLTzMfQPhGbDPuUJJbLePozTwsi+r1xnzNJSpTidYmkNK1NQYwpsZa+qK/GXCgCBjGz1bjFeutpeL+GhJkRQM3iqptbTW+pyTk7pX4hn49rVl/lcYxx1UkUN9BR0xEITk9MMs+5YTVo5lQHWf7p0Mv8q86fis9AcowUCXPhJOx0fL5Yc3p/3me75NWQbgJmWmVOfp7eCH4YrN3E19bM5SoW7SQCG26WLvvBNhmHFgQ3/5xAuooRFIDPI/kC7hsurPtSC4t6f95nu+TVkG4CZlplTn6e9Ie8+fcBTvnnpLQZo/l4x7gOWxx+dlCfYTp35CDq8xrgidrOIBdvCILTjvO7DVdVnDL4L3+NwusIxfj01rc7ilWye5SrPRRLk8fWB+3Hs9S2wY4vAqkICtW5yWU0HtkHGZ/Y6A5/UaHhS44XLP0671C+L2miyAx13AqaW6f/HyxhSQZKquNZlDGalWJz/YqIG5rVnq/1QIWUJTK/5LKKJadZmnZgucXnQdDskWiT5FHcYL8KGAluHVDU+MBm5xzPjd6Gg2f6F0hw8KlhlEtrVHlt93auHPUhKXfQ7rfXGnJcNWmwiahBDCuziWfH55p4b9C+MKcA0fH/vp7HAOFS16+SRJDRGtUE7VanxQnCbKDvRZCoZdq3twTC4WO7rIZmXH6jKCOcCBOfMXL70XVDgElTJ8kmG0kH1sudg6jFIFw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20033","langCode":"vi","question":"t7mbG3kGtRDzr3rcSSd1Sai4KdFolGTB3tAIVJiNgl+dVRKAluSFqLeRtnjfzV5dOFJXMorae5Iygko40Za1bg\u003d\u003d","answers":["the least harmful","the less harmful","the more harmful","less harmful"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+/RF1V7sgM/NXpaAdhEuqkZslmUu6dZ3WBRROy9+vn8BOUhrk8xx82b4EbJT7oB+cFdhu5BXk/2mok2irfV0fNEIusYaidFJtS28Fk8LjrK+5I7CuPbA7nhsgz9uG4fDxccJPOaoe8RwCIF5kL1MCOi8EXHozdsvEB9xpqjhYWYKi2TXA1ZmjQQnANgJQ02sjVuykyrnzW0f8LpDbraXbnUmGgF62gxpznRjaO+q5IWy38zpF+J0QBwfwH/cyqMjaC1YHpcDgNQOXNKeljWr4Nn/lQLGQs0uwaLvj/s/41yrGsXIIwWrm0oJ5OCrlYBImr/BFos1yUrOwCjb/uekRXuWlf95+KmQSM8obb7BRTQ+L9Ct9lcpsCrcmh1tZQrOqMsF4Fn8mzMWD+EvhZdFf7+Y2AbRKn+ob07K3983w2tuRfNvfre3T34dDZ6rzQF0KE/wTCvtUXv1Y/rW6E9DTNUGv/D52AuOjuzlCVRwyF/OghYWBiHMehidLczbh0UiIm6lmfr2jY3wEpfgGE2tDxTPBR4eayA31BNgF4UuaLEf3UTr9t2KmrqpKU8lZxmDvDPz6GCbLSR9zam4ui4VhMLy73x4/5nkHSjlm5qCiYBiSjssOr9iz90ETnTWItao2yP+ujN5WphMr6hgG1zW2UP2JLhb+GzJTALnxRjMpGONAlAL51jkhEAFI8FHdr+Gs5/21Boxyi6AikFgMz8Y7MzFs18udLFkHRKfzWMEpZOprptlgBPxqbrhtx7YJs0oTsHO+GsErNTelWWcz8urVClhIzGRaCN+A43QnF/mu28WRfj3VpjezI+OYflzA8VBnQATexPUnUUJ1x9nERprT2AavEyHC1jx4A5HQXZUQtmUnS+ppLQOGMH5C53vOT65m3w517/rhXGzFALQHWZXMU2jOqpUGf14MxnbmNZ3SEygGrxMhwtY8eAOR0F2VELZmsL9uM5qUvS3pAvnhKOoyfk8zwAaV7ZkDyI+zJg3kOOwF6vri1yR6cMC1lJY0C7tXWEUsaloI4zC7RfOwuEk/EzcYJCz7ou+/1+wtTFTlJ+rrK3wzLeNMGgpDslu51WLBCvATjmPDMkqBVdPxzt31e9weiCvDAV/xtXV5prwh3xE+6Jzhat8iq1NnxC7D41lEQRK0cmuAApEP+T2nE1cBm/MiaOuUdebvZMy+MwVGos1+14TvZXgb7LzYoLasVds9x2rhIZo9dch1XaluHJOqqQzr2N+HsAUjud9PjAXrow3SZKt0f5l5AACdpcM4rNLvGydMWMdDJnrFCx0XBqZZZhRc9gcetogMX0+7S1ihxtkmmd5J+qEOrSHwViyzI0aA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20034","langCode":"vi","question":"3XkjnjJAKDO8G0MU0cPyG4vW8SsK2aGy7b3aj+AkJalJ+FXfsXv3AfUt9NbLMV6dIrE3zyIV7S0TGM0OdhVJSw\u003d\u003d","answers":["as useful","less useful","most useful","more useful"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE92K0fnUVEG0zCgUGU0JKWr5NhwmK3t1loF/G2VuShRb/ItHTFOa5CbLLWnjNZIQ2ASF1pWUGXRLqKjBakYx271IesfoVlfsBk1iq1JcA38EEemm242K1LCos71aOkmPxe+K2V2IX2XPW4s7agcGLjNCtYBkP+bPUE5fucMkCajlKsHk6DB+raVxk6nYTejUVw6S2yrXVbfY4YDt+Q95Tc17rDd21Ek/XDdjgPtn5BGyEs5tKcvp4ItpycQGUEozBkz4QNx9HgM8fqU6CnW3AKz/tx10h9FH9oULCbpt9goZfAQ3zGi4RcnHIU64t2fAr3AZ35+wOMMfY8SKgF7tf/8KeoFkxnyzi0O8K4Kw0GRDXjt4Fohb88Bnv/HLb2GjvGXagOHofOyHyoPHLri+9fSfr/Tde8SSs5P0BW9tAFj3xR22dBzjggOq2zuhzJJUBPaVILJbG9IDndvtx3jTZukx25xw25sE20V5fSB5PCNCvzImjrlHXm72TMvjMFRqLKJmVnalwyS3EGaP+Rod3kToPcFJX3c59R1rMC+fc4etJmW75dGuMcqVy2M+L6MHYiotk1wNWZo0EJwDYCUNNrINjtVs+Ij97JvQyctc+ES8rVmjAYSESFZervaxrmS9Q5QYIWUo1vaE2dQ1YVZXRycl11WPB3puwmto8nABDxr5tzmKNekgSiJUYEinB3UYlG92BR3p1oZ9TwKvLqJz30wnjdoLmPVjwmqnD68J78Tr1YrYIhXXJVJZno84AH0s7pWmzlITMvsT4NvEgvGd/3Gt+MzobaoMyg5/FtZLA9eG+Fc5CIGIm7Iokl4kf2BJH29BkL9v42qJqD64Sf7fO8Y\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20035","langCode":"vi","question":"8MeXJAB/Zse4Jd1OwLCusepA+rhQg9ESP/2Oe25MJ8Lr93gzfAMGAWTW09WmE+K6kQYrhTRpHs0eof99yp0s6Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["more popular","less popular","most popular","so popular"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEy93ZicVhYwW4EK16EsKuAEKPKXPWZpeMXpnQ+uYy8Neqbl9k0e3c40mxAiYlb2knZw325HAH4vPBO0wfgvKpZYCVkUjRHkN+0/4yk5wwSCmClhI8AaPSuD6dPPOEnEQMh6mwRRh1fIU2RvRwtc9gZZsQ0XKWKvhO7DwifuDwfNwc7f07IpX1qc3/hGL1cNGpfsXoSoYr93P05WkKuUlPaGKO+dW7nD2UGuWjhbN6ek259fwnfoooKX/yHywgLIu1crK8AZaK0VLJt+c/NybSLaW5WwnsiuT8locg+JIXv7RVM8BXYnqixWjIuWCnfC01oi2Ejcj8VVajVN8N7m+pU6NE6Z0mil4s0F+DmnAFpF3uxgQJ8VnlE5ZToCvztpOls8vXupXhH9JQbvrN1Xt/LL2Tgeq4M8hbopprWuubUWJwfk7UPftqvD7UepSdWAO9h1hNLVQXCFqnSqHKX2VDdM4chlfd2xbyhQ5Upuy1RWyF0gPcBZ5Z01PFoR78d/dfcwht2aZ/8Wil8AOPip7tqXPBC+3If3+jW/wjGkTjK7Ydvn/IMlPx42VdVtQSh2x0KucujTFRQJt6Tq4xtKXQOFL4DwvKaEDHY/9NdwJbW96Y6CeD7zADNjiscbg2tBxrWMWuxVkHe0fZ5RceDk/vnquf6oOR1nw7MoZUSTqfYL2jDo8CRMhLB6kIj5yR/Y4ZfLjZ2y64pmsmfeStTRuF1ld18uTke3XzV5N4lc1nxRAt7lDqqeuRUT+r6aPvgGhYlT1/3sproK3DNnHCFmbPzjYOkj/gUdi9YCcktmlxVFGaepDtrLtIwgCmAhHZ83Pg4RvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20036","langCode":"vi","question":"b6poBkk7s4/+irGIRGiGONWXf4iBLjZxQN8cN76GZ+s\u003d","answers":["hotter and hot","more and more hot","hotter and hotter","hotter and more hot"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEyxBkQixX8NmESIAV+q5nrHo8g717Zk+78pkAtRV5J/tULLy6vS33+mgY7M6ShsUQXXnLeKLZEnkhbFZADO4pJlfbaVEJWQbbbo+QYTZW6in9FXRAUbtzoVgxaUHxKgWFfaLW4WDpObXLCgRuS+H97uKPHyxC2pn1ZdEMp589JhRTLizdNqNyTu7NDNskA9/IsPRTrogfEop7fNVQ/8W1/MfvQqS0CfzaNksytQLEpWy1ysoUucxRgQ+Eum7io191mn2KHifcA26rWWCIT8hwlVzwwIGLZMh9WFAJEbqBDB6mwaJY2F3fugCWV5iAZ2Od6a9ioP2rPIkvJRUDzH4PRESaYmraJhFwO+bl5Q4fSf/OsGCkqRERKAg7gN869KoBAvHHPszCn7NPngP6lOzjGao9n3hrVSNuMzkapzKbxT+9k4HquDPIW6Kaa1rrm1FiYiNlwVsap66hVLCqpL+/DwMYkgrp1x29DGbcPyNY8Q2FWSYiGG9LHgdnSk2gGlMwLo2z8ubU0bN49g7hbidD/Jbgh2edZidVemfQrkulrd1bRc7qJREam4ygToVKKOCSvUT4ho0hWKCk67gKH0kXv1XPirYwcsEZE7pEbWgfZyMljWH0n9BWTVa6r/iKolh/a8Vph72nQZ5lK8Q1PCRQZ/rGQFwDDI1CjwHYIq3QBhxCdoI92sNeECrtz7Vd3WQHtq4xGoHMdn21g1mbw0Fa39FJ8UsE1DvDNE5l0y6ejhk7oPVX0Gw0pUXhutpdpTOfUIeioXk+zBacDDyh2o3O+0s5tV+C1YyQ0GxukwOdr0909Uiu10hRwTCocMSOFLX/dwO9oVz5lRVDBdr46nvR9Q\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20037","langCode":"vi","question":"4Ooaglgj7RGvLz+qh4zujCjI4c1v8eIn3Px7MSjQxgwPMmFCnG84HMo1CrFxDGok","answers":["more and less interested","more interested and interested","interested and more interested","more and more interested"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+yWpkNcNrmgpeCdAfCvZy7AuI9H3CS1nI4pZ7p0hCqWR6JtYs6zb9ls5xcIgSG+M3zCNuLy4gx7l/A2UwwLnBhKUmuX7Y15K/NuVkEavqDhyVbswxmK02eQ9QbwoVzu7g1TOxNKzGNqEUupA0rKb1y6RJef9TMFGvR86iXFD0DmlWuCnFeOlQ5XxF5WgHEzdxPyuH5mV7TuaeB+damm18mxMRy7vTpF/OmX29sSXUiMeFfjkVfPaXOhzdbWS0RGVmJY/namDCg/vuLN0ehiWX/wHUKW+p3q9Qexnbx9uX4arH9ZnpNrin4h3lOqWZImo1Oggd2jafqhtSUxeWh3XI7AIh3ZOZAtpHVaBqKLVaOTsCEvhM3fxDlxY1YS0g9YFPdbJwUjq7u+tW7mbw61sa/zNQ6zKGmjyFSzUDVfwt7ks06YBpLhcj5kvq5RlKfqXZ+v9N17xJKzk/QFb20AWPe2a3KsAUe47GNtyFKeLJrrTiPvvX+lN9zTD2vMdersBnhISx9eixpo9ePFo40poyPp7xkbcpOOnDqMqPX44H5keWTy4PEFaYWbdlom9Lng+mDLsCZobcIRNFv0MMGBKjo+Y/bK2C0qUXF1y46QzkAe8whrGQY7vqcGilkl0mGM1J8J3BT+knWwacCPQW7bE2+3oB5BO1H+0w1ZX0yt3ssf5XnAfsdqkm8ncrQd5so2/n0C5UVQJqI8VAoLMtLPL8BeYWIBvXeDCQf5GLqOxx/k45wDr4aPlaZwDEs+vyF0/J8/R8r6B9M+o3OaCfh3lCT44jYh1xc0KayLVQStYmiPiRTN27X/OVA5TKJChNqK5T8gvZOBBb28aPNf26wqRI4m+DSrfuYEj+BiArcMmm1p"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20038","langCode":"vi","question":"a7j3OwgOjz2vwXjcifT/z9DnKOvCMG7i2qEE4T29rhe7ZQWGWzEnuMgA7JRDTY0+","answers":["darker/ less cold","dark/cold","darker/ colder","more dark/colder"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEybk+A35NHRe6zRernciFrBU1NNPzLgrazoc9H4Ajfd84bA8V+laP3VEuaYW8opFzOC9FtDv819+CmKbq4HR/0K/lkrfC6LzLBGTY2BVa6xGQH+ycEjUecGc+1yXvjBrCR6mwRRh1fIU2RvRwtc9gZZsQ0XKWKvhO7DwifuDwfNwSk+k7VsuJbeitdq05kKfw70Cv+fth0k2fNuvyZKr2efHEgIqrkwTnibFv0W00Act5WM6nQmXCXhONFVNoyH/IRmQjeAilNt3BiCpbLO0g5sSx9/+/tTDgL5Fau2T6+V5nia65zF4NT4mAhI150nPt5XqETGkk1VGfV32LgpUdJoRc58WVq+XDJ3jqgsu9BvOL9Jw7A/JASOChYBmCX1EVnMy4FEWLa9WG5U7aBp15v6GSd3wS8wdRvRNsFoSY0cvgUYqZV8hHz7Rq06al/regoWaZju4DbiwmimIJ/2qKEu65R9DFYq72/VO8lEaT4/75qb8oNKOqTbMq/H8QG4K+6o8wy15JKhLC4ohTVxF9g7SsfGY6iCtFQ5ks+CPfeG3qjHSvILh7Bxxx59Hg8ds2WZ4NB+Wofvf9GfPeb+CgcV90qajcZVfhS6/HYx/aVcqEOmIEMM6FgVd6Uc3WhnDskzjMLVBeS4qZv5AABhj7VMFY8zvNbS7QzO5sRDVMjRsoSkvftq+i1aUYismOUz87zB9J2+30iptW3zu7LgKcoRvdgUd6daGfU8Cry6ic99MJ43aC5j1Y8Jqpw+vCe/E68CD9erFrSeBSHlBse5rYfnFdYjD3ZG5+xwlUSItubGrQYyFqCCtjTr+D9U6LR4a+g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20039","langCode":"vi","question":"2hHj0/eSxTYxu+ipJ55mKrLoy2dfxAmPABbvSFs0KHolP/ANlhXD4Wz5cy0APG5JekCTc+VuCY/HPKgGBhzZP1FO+gAU1NCyFZhWxTNuC+iEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh","answers":["kind/more generous","kinder/ generous","kinder/less generous","kinder/more generous"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEymfFT1NoZ6NQnxWw6DdCFGM8OYTjMADtH4u++p4IE7BgNefsbwUL86INjiBWJybgJdsXcLF/mFVdULb9bmRtbYRXlLldZSJFE3WkXFnnU4h4UThEMAWRn4O+UXtpXiwe7/wr5hLrO2dh+vAL/JzVVcxXrraXi/hoSZEUDN4qqbW7zlcEF3lzCLBtMOk+pgIdy9CDnZJth/izZtLmblkFyqlHhOImeuOjLon+Xhqd7JclCt5cc5QjyUNmvkyIcYw8urrs578VsKQnRaHkQL2IlcMlRXYZ7DMCKlTjqk4FZQusdGcE07IdSW7kJ8ZKeqfWfXXDshQ5FkHySNPRs7AW+r2Zf4A9JyLp6MPbgvrma1kmtELyuzSuxU9Qgz4Vfy2zDS1zl1Dj6wDMVQplTtLNfMtsW5ZWjPRifIdcHoAOWmdNmTnZ7c44sC00JIz+isMdXEt7jl7EYm2aXtoW93iZbsxNbmbzL5t7sqBgbGjn+bSNA46+GO+1J9cFRrIe5UVMY37EWPkSgFnVDhXddj8tJlBNLeZQtWtSQX8edbGJzSj179G49lYfSRtBkEeQV5VxgvFJErjD4jsbbe4rF+Am2Uo9Wvbqe4hy0lrif7IWdHLcKNOzNrDDaB9Mi/m7UpWm4UStr3JaTsYlYDa1VuJ1hVmeDQflqH73/Rnz3m/goHFeYhIPmzuMm2R/xLBlmmEn2DhWaw2/x9HrmzvkEN65TEyhCHqyhoyK5IAzxiiSFmW1wXJ71YqqMPvFCnTv8O56XXUz7JkWRbkO4Q1n0cw6X9WPWDD72UrnxDIi2VIUjrJ5wUe+RRm5Xij1ZQ005dgXS/IpZAbVrqDtxQH4apweQReYWIBvXeDCQf5GLqOxx/k45wDr4aPlaZwDEs+vyF0/BpF0Hf5PQx+hZJx/p5TCI+tirVV+wV7/8x1xu0Xzi8Ax7nERHEMFakpljyD10wL2sBAWvziZ0Hgix1DQeeYXly0bVQ11by8m80xpp0CqqJxGaJ0RjrdTwZPXNianCkgyCI92ET/wfbBteC6db5ppA8\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20040","langCode":"vi","question":"z2m0XNrBUydJZLNs1qwwOKpPG3OStKT6Nhbnzk/nO37bShGzNRCipUTM8jG6MW6u","answers":["fashionable/more attractive","fashionable/attractive","more fashionable/more attractive","more fashionable/attractive"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9tDDd3I5EiqdMW6yEpPI9RQmJWJuM0Fd6jAAiK2cWMf9pDWbY1QALcC37nfQhKBYiDt1E3R1Ulf3/OIlagdAZiKCjtyDqhXcobepDwHLHoOg2fqfXmELJe7VmN0eGJCFiqRL/A/l5XXwOsbG8peLiGk/O9jW3mNUgHbxHSrVwwwFVmomapXP2YviavKNRbf2AcJ1IBjaRSeb7ZLBSq0hizy9be+4rII/8wBfmKbQTh+RvRtFOXopd8lJ4guM/GlMGzgb2Vak6JBqJy6M2FBrvgNwta5glNFdq3QL4oKlKbRmBPUIiY8nLDNzr9o81clrE6B7Cz1xlvuDLQcWbDhq7wH4lat/kM0+70Z/veUMhGo6b8AWLsE1kb6Kr/O1SPlzhdiwbGjzeIfzIIrrE3WeVBCGEBcsxY2oaarNKtS7VO4py3rXaqgwXBkA1afleCuwPscORCNToxDoWndLRW0NCRxYTXfCjwI1IDBq4UHWnEi4jRYrQhG53P0bMjWt3HnAMcf9xIW/MyzEYmxWHzjWSnBRxFY/iD9ZJYiIN6QH3ztXmDfIMpACu2ocQEaA/WoFWJouKWh/HTfKl0rGzjkknWhI3uauj90aGtP1B8zXuWhIh527DRDfH50Mh+UvmMX7cYQlvyNCv4feTPBLrL+YWa+sGO8yyWQJrWUPyRR6JNa7JZHFvLQud8GB51HQ5YoA5tx3krzupUO87l2QLvE8MDooMIF6UUUz57LLaMZm/Y2wA20vsKI8XLxaqmJCzf3EtCsR24XcLOmEMIzgUhkU1YlJvQgOAGoksJO+MV7umzXpDxDGxXmjDVUlpO1d6dZTgSIMTWqoOXp2crSK3mdfjiR8EFP4YoC7JBh/XJsnXvv5KOEI4VbYhnkNJBQsVmOfEVAOplpRNncPAXggNhBtNM\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20041","langCode":"vi","question":"w7967AiNF8D5WhPUvh7AcCc/w0C/WHKW1uotdu35lpm0Eqh3UsGMHagLUWar90znd6wVZS53bl/Y8DHdZVORkA\u003d\u003d","answers":["more complicated/less interested","complicated/ interested","complicated/less interested","more complicated/interested"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7ukdiGHReEwNrlhiHo1MAnl/64yYsGlqwxItvVxcWS3ZOSYdoiSYqdXYs3twRAk1SDt1E3R1Ulf3/OIlagdAZiKCjtyDqhXcobepDwHLHoOg2fqfXmELJe7VmN0eGJCFiqRL/A/l5XXwOsbG8peLiGk/O9jW3mNUgHbxHSrVwwwFVmomapXP2YviavKNRbf2AcJ1IBjaRSeb7ZLBSq0hizy9be+4rII/8wBfmKbQTh+RvRtFOXopd8lJ4guM/GlMGzgb2Vak6JBqJy6M2FBrvgNwta5glNFdq3QL4oKlKbRmBPUIiY8nLDNzr9o81clrE6B7Cz1xlvuDLQcWbDhq7wH4lat/kM0+70Z/veUMhGo6b8AWLsE1kb6Kr/O1SPlzhdiwbGjzeIfzIIrrE3WeVBCGEBcsxY2oaarNKtS7VO4py3rXaqgwXBkA1afleCuwPscORCNToxDoWndLRW0NCRxYTXfCjwI1IDBq4UHWnEi4jRYrQhG53P0bMjWt3HnAMcf9xIW/MyzEYmxWHzjWSnBRxFY/iD9ZJYiIN6QH3ztXmDfIMpACu2ocQEaA/WoFewWEhio8+xtNnwCDZdbQoffMaXc+TNYN6wpi4n4EKEXovJu8NhAgMyOc7qjMWTQyY8rZLIjzcyqDLc1bzzaKd4wRcCNY2701j0E9vQWsm+DF//V1I/zn+twSEhm3QKwP+mQuT2GWNHWMXcqo1Djh3S0Dh90ZC/NQ0TSqtqbs0pukhKnS52onI+nmzDzEF+zozB9J2+30iptW3zu7LgKcoRvdgUd6daGfU8Cry6ic99MJ43aC5j1Y8Jqpw+vCe/E64hBky4XuvZuKN4nb6EIb+d8pGft8TV49tX9eXi142v7eN1118CkvBNb5k5kZ+xf2k0+U9LY3TAU8LlWIriK+K5sKC3Vdip9v+T+BtuQpOfL"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20042","langCode":"vi","question":"GInwLlWCNpwNQkSV+uwsyQLdz7wAQRiTjGErY1JKn+r4wdPLqPaRiNubkO03Aj8VCgHFa1EDfLHghPZYTXMq3A\u003d\u003d","answers":["to be used","to use","using","use"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE2XYMqa1wGznovwZy6ut1UoGlLfdXkyqSB4JkSEuU72Xq53kMOVEbiuMFSkpDOLo0rr7vUPLStjiBip1vB4nqw4tmpm5TqiuTkowFyF7Ug6yKnN+n2HcLL+UEy63fITUg8xtJQd6xb7Jcjw2wowd27SGsuW2sGp3PrFu9UW3W4aWuWlgpRM8W/jHbZi6LbrqFYo8MCFzwPhpJsedwtwQHBGE58zuFoxw++cvvWrFt6me9/RsRSMaa7avWIeoJve4dw3Y3rj20/L96zjmllBmefXPu+UaKuta4p0Si/Kgzn3Wsqpg1V8OFuv/62ZOiHUZDTbNRcXfCXmGwZok4NE5UheLg+Oqm9XKOVzwkGVW9d8PQEoLktV27A/lFu8Nb9Tf/70uk2ZWzeGCIBklJm1PyWER9kPnFEhzYN4+QNdUp7dEmCCMK+7akaZD+5MM6VG2/cNke3vV/xC3elcpJJXYGmq4/yBHtOd9RhtXbRveoMO5uCJ2s4gF28IgtOO87sNV1WcMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuJAOdBlth8HprdHt7OIbjF/SjyrlepXSeLskI29cXL3LVOIb42FJ3ryMgk2hfAiYIuEeTVP5WPvXlg983L6eFrBN0OrGigk2K6wBA+N3HLNR+kHWkU5iN+Fm4Sve0YOTIGUyCsH6A4lEfgvSlzod0mRciK845Cb12ysqkQNu/605aXC6SVXLVeLC7abRAxbmkBEg7y8HpSOL0IlcW1w3ITOVkPDREuh97mlHJ+sV/Cap90mSrdH+ZeQAAnaXDOKzS7xsnTFjHQyZ6xQsdFwamWWYUXPYHHraIDF9Pu0tYocbcGAorC7Kk09GKGC492BwA8p/v/0+wajtLHD+yrSewZx"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20043","langCode":"vi","question":"FHY83cNnFihA0q/cjizTZ7v999FOFKKCy5AJP/HKAT/tSdwVxYFKu5DzOArzY0UhVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["two year older","two years older","two years","two older"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9gByXK4Jtz8ZWgnKQa3wjLIaR+uPXWOm2/52oSnw6uZYPhA4ou/fhjDAS2E33v+MdnGXV64nU44NrwHosbsSQKzN2j1iiqox9xE7ArDu2JB7q3G5XbX3SgEWZC6QTrtYrUxkoGLGRaT8rJCGPn5tGVzNg6i2nPUwk+PxmlAk9WeYHXtaytAsVIxie3/iJmp+rHv6dqlWmSxnFzJxXaYbHWBxKprVBb+j83JkolUwZ/MWXmrP9v2AEtmlWnQqSPzkr6wY7zLJZAmtZQ/JFHok1rslkcW8tC53wYHnUdDligDPp9AsOFbHLnNG9L8/wsLeDNu2689ljZaDg099x1HVLTpTKBIlE2FiFrQquTEyrRq2DY6byUbF2K5py7PJJIXbylYTpaZ788FGpcJ/07fky+fzxXmcIIdUBWMeviBm8c6qzI3C8llzEew04p/04P4hdiUTvxE7p72R4ufOvRRiTGCpxzau1KsiYP/Grb6xowKtVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20044","langCode":"vi","question":"Qr52aSqqcJ5hkPDHxnBqIgrqD3IWBd3N5NNfCTlbvO5RVf8ZMRClxylOEnUenXRU","answers":["three times as much than","three as much as","three times much than","three times as much as"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeExNy4XsLxMXLHdbpTaAMUoGKJ0lOn8ZiAcCXU7H2ttkwumR/M/iQxmW7r9KwVjUhXKa6bZYAT8am64bce2CbNKHyGZFWdtRQW1G2Cm0Eevq5qAGmdoscqbmKJUE9wpiAmOfoYxTmoDVupnvrbOnqvQylsLZorHBs/PvZ4wRF68Q1+PpKttzIl7mS8bABj5y4BFhxOuIuDZ+qScvksvBnKb/AztrlZ8rZ4q9IFEMfPuHkwdz9x06nigKr+DSStizc3ZnaEKO1Y1AnaKHyL1Pq2yizckbTYV1tKib5rNJp3yLcNX24NRg4AoIhqs77/EE4w/5V6r2pYVN0mPoFc7QNROiH+G/jYHLHNZItsdGLkSvpH9rBxpNB5ayKEoKqomV7xbAb5DC7uJ3xDfJG8l8mW6phZY5ZeBlmNcTpRo5aqIF2kfeb5IUwzQW48a/VB9PnfFwTFzjD5YO55Ebftftrz6Y6e8WKhzarSh+HPe62GlHlhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20045","langCode":"vi","question":"4zg+WIpo1uupFPL+2HtWfaR5VE5u8cdyV1JpmD+h++JUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["two as many craps as","twice as many craps than","two many craps as","twice as many craps as"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5WNF0SC1VPjEcp59VxcjUJFSp/I6iXYrKqTn42Z75BJumR/M/iQxmW7r9KwVjUhXKa6bZYAT8am64bce2CbNKHyGZFWdtRQW1G2Cm0Eevq5qAGmdoscqbmKJUE9wpiAmOfoYxTmoDVupnvrbOnqvQylsLZorHBs/PvZ4wRF68Q1+PpKttzIl7mS8bABj5y4BFhxOuIuDZ+qScvksvBnKb/AztrlZ8rZ4q9IFEMfPuHkwdz9x06nigKr+DSStizc3ZnaEKO1Y1AnaKHyL1Pq2yiyCMIA8okAlr+d867lUdz9UJDXnP/Pw0Em7t3kXOmsZv5V6r2pYVN0mPoFc7QNROiH+G/jYHLHNZItsdGLkSvpH9rBxpNB5ayKEoKqomV7xUbLrxw4cTSvXjH9kb+u3A+DQKYTYDdgJHcvZtKlS6y39HDSFPLRXfmEz/WNLcCDpXq/CoYs/EFifIUxVH3l+N8\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20046","langCode":"vi","question":"+HIOR9kNbdFeKk9QqlidJ6ta7UiFojfz694UvWMl2kI\u003d","answers":["less apples","few apples","least apples","fewer apples"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE900R2xxdzTOtjXgFfM7Jc+aJ1KsKfz9ZPXOqXnGpJmRrNi/pO4xHojRxa++s9jt2mJLby/iPYLW0PutZ1kq0uqWqHsDZuZub4q5iI0MZ5fL9oxDPrXein5+IURnWloiWoO9maY6VhadZ0wm17sl7YgepsEUYdXyFNkb0cLXPYGWbENFylir4Tuw8In7g8HzcCOaa8zpI/HrZS0njnLyNmfiboa9ilOMwOmgyroyWoPhoNfRA9qQ43XjB0Rnc7vItwvr/D18PYmaRICWJhbI3PJVtWE1lM5YIeiEpaVFu8MhfBVqNT0XTnW/LWLXMM4j+ujbWXj5KKZtovIG0ZGt1v5HKLxfeREja1iDl5X7D5yPia+gIK/PvsF4V0ZC5b2IuH+uv45GTenJr5tgXESNl6mIlKsx+uBLDwtEUMlOYEEYEKhUjgxYaCX43AVH3+29ARll+ijAJe+juitIA+vUc41ZR5N3xPzBy+hZFn3fRSpGH3p/hiTtagN6VGWHdaDLEjIt6z80paQRhrWL1faWM/pHOqFYnrqabTkVsAXA2lP8"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20047","langCode":"vi","question":"LciKtYtre4OfCTVsXu1Zgx1YlcmYX3UCUq4xO41IJJk\u003d","answers":["least","fewer","less free time","few"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwpb9sY1dbq6GRiqPhQdUJBqUpwVXmhq8iprF6VCIDXIn0oMyJxyDnh87lWRTF37RHrWMDB3CbXBDDG+d26EpQOWqHsDZuZub4q5iI0MZ5fL7SGNTHs96tKxldk17O0wGGTkwLYC9mcss4In3WoIWN1iKMZ3r9IzNw8S7xxde/nynbI0C08dNmBnG+wlsGhxWSBDTtFAZn+l0IDLmuEzf10VED4Nsg2hoMODnNlCI8s5NYwDcWHuCZADWf/1FklzXXQsg0+K4Z8rwD3F7uFp7m69kJgV0PsmrdPOOesB6LAjwNx2evhEraS5v+UDjYpiYSzQUE8y6Ptl7dseoS4DqldiTnR434cpBFEkmMARqkHl8Wroa3Ku4op+4OSPJJO+HEyNBvKmhjcqLsAn6vd1tI89hZ+41cpbi91u5CflguYm5dm5qqBe+vYLR0T8pxvi3cBer64tckenDAtZSWNAu7V1hFLGpaCOMwu0XzsLhJPx4JCEgrgIy+GL6Xc8zc2fNTrnuhvh6IHc63CDFngITCU8hcx8DvMjHVyw2Dg/vUJWhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20048","langCode":"vi","question":"1p80LWkZuFMlG+GdG/rgADhdln6oCq9DzB3RnkzbIrJYGnDcG/VJcBj77XI4zcQ2","answers":["more and less people","more and more person","more and more people","few and few"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+yWpkNcNrmgpeCdAfCvZy7n/8MKxHqzcwnmGkldTF02XRyo+MmbK97PX/q7d1p12QjnZ5JGzTe1fWPtpNsNPhkFhSEnnTqp3L/BpXk9/ppHT8RmqDqBLcpQHG9WgbgbrXeEPv0WybwCddlQ3GSJdsrGoTHN4l20xoByatRU3x9Iow2/TTb1c5sCXMG9BQt31d5ZF/NBBgGEHWC/tiSYOuKgq4KYC35MC1i/LR5n/lAIX28EaZ2Se7OAcqB5flsstGukXW48soJ6nYgE0e+la4nQ97onX/PX1vPTHMkljVQfdeipPPxaTbeeVDk/KLt8x8lGbHsz8/arAYerwWpS/15wfMWnOOH9ywDaeeaUwKxQQMTvk65h5RGaD7mU5KaecH8MD6gsW4vzxdSQO+9UbaAXlHnkjYo916zcMkxus6JSA6U/pzpKn6Og0nFJI7V2UI4zN04DxasX56TP7+XD51KwSEE49zvGA2cxKBKbrqxf"},{"topicId":"20","id":"20049","langCode":"vi","question":"iFrd/pRZZvJ2fqWYhtwMgoXrVfeygRMSW8aiMhlfllI\u003d","answers":["few and less students","Less and more students","less and less students","few and few students"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE74rPzLBEAfv63jSnJ1b0Fc+BWN4luy76gVxQ/xs67eVwQ6eCLmAe2C03AkBKyjZUAwaReTRUb6yEC9OEojLLZByhNJeUu61jn7ZPVBZf0UR5MlsQk/NE4LE3tE29dUBH80ozF6+j/eaeOgnHfxt+nlYqev4ZpufT0UT8CYHRZkf69raFCgF5hQsQFzGOruI/2cZJ+07HC9UVzTe8CrYngBpl8KLlmScEj0yK/xMqwOnExPwo5tylp0w2rz34+UI0W+0TM1OgMud4mHjDnk5p1HlF8mPnse2Vf0ssAMRBvtV5cY+8KK46hI0zwt9WhA8iso1/3HHiP3QDEyhK7U3wjHUYdf37M29ZT3EJMGjddEhUOQUf8r7OUlewfxrN2jOrceck84pN7OED5FVlqxAEmr7iXvthXAhkf3FTwVlIBDLjDWX8NeUnsuunxHLG9wArt4f1ILA5u0CLKF/pCsWQuj1dglWiKSJ2i+sRnvGreQ5"}]